<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<resources>
    <string name="CFBundleDisplayName">Love2Love</string>
    <string name="CFBundleName">CoupleApp</string>
    <string name="format_two_params">%1$@ %2$@</string>
    <string name="format_slash_separator">%1$@ / %2$@</string>
    <string name="format_comma_separator">%1$@, %2$@</string>
    <string name="NSLocationWhenInUseUsageDescription">Love2Love uses your location to calculate the distance between you and your partner, and to allow you to add places to your shared memories.</string>
    <string name="NSPhotoLibraryUsageDescription">Love2Love needs access to your photos to allow you to personalize your profile and add images to your shared memories in the couple\'s journal.</string>
    <string name="NSUserNotificationsUsageDescription">Love2Love sends you notifications when your partner sends you a message. You can disable these notifications at any time in Settings.</string>
    <string name="access_photos">Access Photos</string>
    <string name="activate_notifications_button">Activate notifications</string>
    <string name="activate_notifications_onboarding">Activate notifications</string>
    <string name="ad_10">What song makes you feel like I\'m next to you?</string>
    <string name="ad_100">What has positively surprised you in our long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_101">What do you appreciate about our way of handling disagreements together?</string>
    <string name="ad_102">What would you tell your past self about distance and love?</string>
    <string name="ad_103">If you could make me appear for an hour, what would you do with that moment?</string>
    <string name="ad_104">What thing would you like to experience with me for the first time?</string>
    <string name="ad_105">What are the three things that bring us closer despite everything?</string>
    <string name="ad_106">What question would you like me to ask you more often?</string>
    <string name="ad_107">How could we ensure that each feels respected and heard during difficult discussions?</string>
    <string name="ad_108">Are there values or principles you consider essential in a long-term relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_109">What\'s the last time you felt a physical longing for me?</string>
    <string name="ad_11">What do you miss most when you think of me?</string>
    <string name="ad_110">What does success mean to you, personally, and what does that look like in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_111">What activity would you like us to start together online?</string>
    <string name="ad_112">When do you think about me most during the day?</string>
    <string name="ad_113">If we couldn\'t write to each other for a week, what would you tell me before?</string>
    <string name="ad_114">What photo of me do you look at when you miss me too much?</string>
    <string name="ad_115">What do you think about our compatibility regarding our future aspirations?</string>
    <string name="ad_116">How do you feel about our life goals and how they align?</string>
    <string name="ad_117">Would you like me to send you a love letter?</string>
    <string name="ad_118">What crazy idea would you like us to realize together someday?</string>
    <string name="ad_119">What are the things you hope we\'ll be able to look back on with pride in the future?</string>
    <string name="ad_12">How do you feel about sharing deep thoughts? Are there topics you\'d like us to address more often?</string>
    <string name="ad_120">Don\'t you think distance makes our ability to communicate grow?</string>
    <string name="ad_121">Do you think we should call each other more often?</string>
    <string name="ad_122">Don\'t you think we handle this distance between us quite well?</string>
    <string name="ad_123">What do you think of the quote \'out of sight, close to heart\'?</string>
    <string name="ad_124">If we could call each other every day at the same time, when would you choose?</string>
    <string name="ad_125">Don\'t you think we can still be proud of ourselves? And our efforts?</string>
    <string name="ad_126">Do you think about me often, or very often?</string>
    <string name="ad_127">What do you think about promising that we\'ll make the necessary efforts to continue together?</string>
    <string name="ad_128">What do you think makes us unique as a couple?</string>
    <string name="ad_129">How has our relationship evolved since we started being together?</string>
    <string name="ad_13">How do you feel when we can\'t talk?</string>
    <string name="ad_130">How would you describe our love to someone who doesn\'t understand long-distance relationships?</string>
    <string name="ad_131">What\'s one thing I could improve in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_132">How do I make you feel loved and appreciated, even at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_133">What\'s your most beautiful dream where I was with you?</string>
    <string name="ad_134">What have you discovered about love by living a long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_135">If you could spend a whole night with me, what would you like us to do?</string>
    <string name="ad_136">Don\'t you think we hold onto love even more when we\'re at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_137">How do you react when someone talks to you about me?</string>
    <string name="ad_138">What would be your ideal way to spend time together during my next visit?</string>
    <string name="ad_139">If there was only one place in the world I could take you, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="ad_14">What moment shared with me comforts you when you\'re alone?</string>
    <string name="ad_140">If there was one thing you could change about me, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="ad_141">What distinguishes me from other people in your life?</string>
    <string name="ad_142">What don\'t you tell me often enough, but feel deeply?</string>
    <string name="ad_143">Are there books or movies that make you think of us as a couple?</string>
    <string name="ad_144">What\'s your favorite moment in our calls or messages?</string>
    <string name="ad_145">Have you ever felt that our bond transcends even the kilometers?</string>
    <string name="ad_146">What habit would you like me to keep even when we\'re finally reunited?</string>
    <string name="ad_147">What do you feel when you look at our old messages or photos?</string>
    <string name="ad_148">What place represents our long-distance love for you?</string>
    <string name="ad_149">Do our values align when it comes to relationships and life goals?</string>
    <string name="ad_15">Have you ever dreamed of me? What happened in that dream?</string>
    <string name="ad_150">What kind of adventure would you like us to live together right now, if it were possible?</string>
    <string name="ad_151">What words of mine have stayed with you and that you sometimes recall in your mind?</string>
    <string name="ad_152">Do you find that I really manage to understand you well?</string>
    <string name="ad_153">What would be the perfect surprise to give me during my next visit?</string>
    <string name="ad_154">What do you want to write about me in your diary or personal notes?</string>
    <string name="ad_155">What makes us unique compared to other long-distance couples?</string>
    <string name="ad_156">Do I make enough effort to understand your emotions even at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_157">How often should we plan time for fun activities like playing games online or watching a movie together?</string>
    <string name="ad_158">When was the last time I really made you laugh?</string>
    <string name="ad_159">What\'s your greatest certainty about the two of us?</string>
    <string name="ad_16">What would you like us to do together at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_160">What\'s something special about me that no one else knows, but you appreciate?</string>
    <string name="ad_161">How would you like me to respond when you tell me you miss me?</string>
    <string name="ad_162">If there was a series that represents both of us, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="ad_163">Do you have a recent story where someone made you think of me?</string>
    <string name="ad_164">What emotions are most intense for you in this long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_165">Are our dreams for the future perfectly compatible? If not, how can we adjust them to align?</string>
    <string name="ad_166">What shared memories between us are particularly meaningful, regardless of distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_167">Do you remember the moment you fell in love with me?</string>
    <string name="ad_168">What\'s your favorite thing about me?</string>
    <string name="ad_169">If you had to send me a memory in a box, which one would you put in it?</string>
    <string name="ad_17">Are there topics you\'d prefer us to avoid?</string>
    <string name="ad_170">What do you think is the most important thing for keeping a long-distance relationship strong?</string>
    <string name="ad_171">What photo would you like us to take as soon as we reunite?</string>
    <string name="ad_172">What\'s your greatest strength in this long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_173">What would be the ideal romantic gift for you?</string>
    <string name="ad_174">What\'s the message you reread when you miss me a lot?</string>
    <string name="ad_175">If we wrote a letter to open in a year, what would you want to read in it?</string>
    <string name="ad_176">What do you think about virtual dates? Do you think we should organize them more often?</string>
    <string name="ad_177">If you had to describe me to someone else, what would you say?</string>
    <string name="ad_178">What was your greatest proof of trust toward me?</string>
    <string name="ad_179">What has most positively surprised you about our way of handling distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_18">Do you prefer exchanging messages throughout the day or having one long conversation?</string>
    <string name="ad_180">Do you think a long-distance relationship can stay strong if we communicate a lot?</string>
    <string name="ad_181">What makes our story different from other couples?</string>
    <string name="ad_182">Do you think we would have been a couple in high school?</string>
    <string name="ad_183">If I was having a bad day, what would you do to cheer me up?</string>
    <string name="ad_184">Do you see me in your future?</string>
    <string name="ad_185">Where would you like to be in 10 years?</string>
    <string name="ad_186">What do you miss most about our physical proximity?</string>
    <string name="ad_187">If you could organize a perfect date for the two of us, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="ad_188">What part of me do you find most attractive?</string>
    <string name="ad_189">How has our relationship changed you positively?</string>
    <string name="ad_19">Is there a place you dream of visiting with me someday?</string>
    <string name="ad_190">What\'s the thing in our relationship you\'d never want to see change?</string>
    <string name="ad_191">What\'s the thing in our relationship you\'d like to see change?</string>
    <string name="ad_192">What time of day do you feel our bond the most?</string>
    <string name="ad_193">What word of love always makes you smile, even at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_194">What dream would you like us to make real together in less than a year?</string>
    <string name="ad_195">If you could write a letter to our future selves, what would you say?</string>
    <string name="ad_196">What\'s the moment when you missed me the most?</string>
    <string name="ad_197">What is there in our relationship that makes you feel truly loved?</string>
    <string name="ad_198">What do you feel when we say \'I love you\' to each other?</string>
    <string name="ad_199">How do you think our relationship will evolve over time?</string>
    <string name="ad_2">What\'s your favorite way to nurture our bond despite the kilometers?</string>
    <string name="ad_20">What\'s the first thing you\'ll do when seeing me again?</string>
    <string name="ad_200">If we had to tell our long-distance story in a movie, how would it start?</string>
    <string name="ad_201">What makes our love stronger than the distance that separates us?</string>
    <string name="ad_202">What would you want me to never forget about you?</string>
    <string name="ad_203">What do you feel when I write you an unexpected message?</string>
    <string name="ad_204">What\'s one thing I do that makes you feel loved, even from far away?</string>
    <string name="ad_205">What\'s the thing in our relationship that makes you happiest?</string>
    <string name="ad_206">What\'s one thing you\'ve always wanted us to do together, but we haven\'t done yet?</string>
    <string name="ad_207">How do you think we\'ve evolved as a couple since the beginning of our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_208">What memory of us always makes you smile?</string>
    <string name="ad_209">How do you think our long-distance relationship has made us stronger?</string>
    <string name="ad_21">How would you feel if we sometimes used silence as a way to \'be together\' despite the distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_210">What message have you most enjoyed receiving from me so far?</string>
    <string name="ad_211">How would you describe the invisible bond that unites us?</string>
    <string name="ad_212">What do you feel when we talk about our future together?</string>
    <string name="ad_213">How can we save money so we can see each other more often?</string>
    <string name="ad_214">What do you think is the most important quality to have in a long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_215">What lesson did we learn last month about our relationship that could help us this month?</string>
    <string name="ad_216">What special occasions are approaching? How do we want to celebrate them?</string>
    <string name="ad_217">What long-distance gift idea would you like to receive from me?</string>
    <string name="ad_218">Do you trust me?</string>
    <string name="ad_219">Do you think I trust you?</string>
    <string name="ad_22">How would you react if one of us had to travel or be very busy for a long period?</string>
    <string name="ad_220">What timeframe seems reasonable to you for us to finally live together?</string>
    <string name="ad_221">How has distance helped us grow individually?</string>
    <string name="ad_222">What advice would you give to someone living a long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_223">What\'s one thing you\'d like to learn to do this year?</string>
    <string name="ad_224">What would be the best time for our reunion for you?</string>
    <string name="ad_225">What\'s one thing you\'d like us to learn together?</string>
    <string name="ad_226">What do you feel when you hear my name in a conversation?</string>
    <string name="ad_227">What moment spent with me helps you keep your spirits up today?</string>
    <string name="ad_228">Are you sometimes jealous? In what situations?</string>
    <string name="ad_229">What\'s the thing you like least about our long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_23">What have you learned about yourself since we\'ve been long-distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_230">What\'s the thing you prefer about our long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_231">If our child lived a long-distance relationship someday, would you support them? What three pieces of advice would you give them?</string>
    <string name="ad_232">What do you most look forward to when we\'re finally together?</string>
    <string name="ad_233">What about long-distance relationships is easier than you expected?</string>
    <string name="ad_234">Do you feel loved?</string>
    <string name="ad_235">What would you like me to never stop, even when we live together?</string>
    <string name="ad_236">How would you feel if I wrote you a handwritten love letter?</string>
    <string name="ad_237">What word would you invent to talk about what we live together at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_238">What can I do to make you feel special even when we can\'t be together?</string>
    <string name="ad_239">How has our love evolved since our first exchanges?</string>
    <string name="ad_24">What letter or message from me do you keep precious?</string>
    <string name="ad_240">What moment from one of our calls marked you the most?</string>
    <string name="ad_241">What season of the year makes you most want to have me near you?</string>
    <string name="ad_242">What kind of romantic evenings could we integrate into our long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_243">What do you think is my most beautiful quality?</string>
    <string name="ad_244">Do you think I\'m a good partner?</string>
    <string name="ad_245">Do you find that we\'re grateful enough for the efforts we both make?</string>
    <string name="ad_246">Since we\'ve been in a long-distance relationship, do you think you\'ve grown as a person?</string>
    <string name="ad_247">What long-distance challenge have you managed to overcome thanks to our love?</string>
    <string name="ad_248">Is there an aspect of yourself you\'d like to change?</string>
    <string name="ad_249">When the day comes, how would you like to celebrate the end of distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_25">What would you like me to do to reassure you when you doubt?</string>
    <string name="ad_250">What goals would you like us to set as a couple for this year?</string>
    <string name="ad_251">If our relationship had a scent, what would it be like?</string>
    <string name="ad_252">What do you most look forward to this year?</string>
    <string name="ad_253">On a scale of 1 to 10, how much is your love for me?</string>
    <string name="ad_254">Did any of my answers surprise you?</string>
    <string name="ad_255">What would you like us to promise each other today, even at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_256">What memory would you like to tell someday about our long-distance relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_26">What small habit could we adopt to make you feel more secure in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_27">Is there a series or movie you absolutely want to watch with me?</string>
    <string name="ad_28">How do you imagine our future together despite the distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_29">Are there insecurities that come up for you in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_3">What small long-distance ritual brings you closest to me?</string>
    <string name="ad_30">What would you like to know about me to feel more comfortable or confident?</string>
    <string name="ad_31">What small word from me has marked you recently?</string>
    <string name="ad_32">What would you like me to send you as a surprise?</string>
    <string name="ad_33">What promise would you like us to make?</string>
    <string name="ad_34">What would you think about sharing passwords for streaming accounts or other small things?</string>
    <string name="ad_35">Do you have an object that makes you think of me?</string>
    <string name="ad_36">How do you feel after a call with me?</string>
    <string name="ad_37">Are there subjects you don\'t dare approach, even with me?</string>
    <string name="ad_38">What would make you feel secure and valued in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_39">What intimate thing would you like us to try together when we reunite?</string>
    <string name="ad_4">What beautiful thing has this distance revealed in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_40">What small gestures make you feel loved and appreciated?</string>
    <string name="ad_41">Have you ever felt a magical moment with me even at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_42">What do you admire most about me?</string>
    <string name="ad_43">How would you feel about us sending each other small gifts or letters from time to time?</string>
    <string name="ad_44">How do you manage to stay confident in us?</string>
    <string name="ad_45">What does \'being present despite the distance\' mean to you?</string>
    <string name="ad_46">What makes our relationship unique even at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_47">What voice message has marked you the most?</string>
    <string name="ad_48">What makes you feel special or valued when we\'re not physically together?</string>
    <string name="ad_49">Do you feel we share enough moments of emotional proximity?</string>
    <string name="ad_5">What\'s the first thing you dream of doing as soon as we\'re reunited?</string>
    <string name="ad_50">Look up quantum entanglement on the internet and tell me if you think this principle also applies to our love?</string>
    <string name="ad_51">How do you imagine our relationship evolving over the coming year?</string>
    <string name="ad_52">How would you feel about making future plans together, even if they\'re just tentative?</string>
    <string name="ad_53">How could you surprise me at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_54">How do you think we\'ll make big decisions once we live in the same place?</string>
    <string name="ad_55">Do you have a phrase or quote that represents our love?</string>
    <string name="ad_56">How has our love evolved at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_57">If you could send me an emotion, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="ad_58">How would you feel if we had to postpone our plans to be together?</string>
    <string name="ad_59">Is it important to you that we plan specific steps in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_6">What unexpected attention would you like to receive from me at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_60">Which ones could we plan?</string>
    <string name="ad_61">What\'s the most beautiful proof of love you\'ve received from me at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_62">What\'s a dream you\'d like us to realize together someday?</string>
    <string name="ad_63">How could we support each other in our dreams and ambitions?</string>
    <string name="ad_64">How important is personal growth to you in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_65">What do you think when you look at a photo of us?</string>
    <string name="ad_66">How has our relationship transformed you?</string>
    <string name="ad_67">What\'s your favorite memory of the two of us?</string>
    <string name="ad_68">How do you feel about talking openly about personal development with me?</string>
    <string name="ad_69">What skill or hobby would you like us to learn together someday?</string>
    <string name="ad_7">What word or message touched your heart despite the distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_70">Is there something you\'re working toward that we haven\'t talked about yet?</string>
    <string name="ad_71">How would our relationship have been different without the distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_72">What do you do to cope with loneliness when we can\'t be together?</string>
    <string name="ad_73">Have you ever been afraid we\'d drift apart because of the distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_74">How do you get through days when you miss me too much?</string>
    <string name="ad_75">What unexpected thing made you think of me recently?</string>
    <string name="ad_76">If you could send me a hug by magic, at what time of day would you do it?</string>
    <string name="ad_77">What quality of our couple seems even stronger than the distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_78">What would you think about us setting \'self-care days\' where each takes time to recharge?</string>
    <string name="ad_79">What tradition could we create for special occasions, even at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_8">What long-distance activity helps you feel most connected to me?</string>
    <string name="ad_80">Have you ever felt an intense connection even kilometers away from me?</string>
    <string name="ad_81">If you could spend a whole day with me, what would we do?</string>
    <string name="ad_82">What message do you like to receive from me when you wake up?</string>
    <string name="ad_83">What special date would you want us to celebrate despite the distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_84">What do you think about planning \'virtual escapes\' together, like spending a weekend watching documentaries?</string>
    <string name="ad_85">How has our relationship helped you grow personally?</string>
    <string name="ad_86">What phrase reassures you when you doubt us?</string>
    <string name="ad_87">What would you like me to do someday just to surprise you?</string>
    <string name="ad_88">What common dream would you want us to realize together?</string>
    <string name="ad_89">What do you think about documenting our memories, like in a shared journal or photo album?</string>
    <string name="ad_9">How would you describe an ideal conversation with me?</string>
    <string name="ad_90">What helps you stay optimistic about our future?</string>
    <string name="ad_91">How do you feel about keeping little objects or mementos from each other to feel more connected?</string>
    <string name="ad_92">How do you feel about managing disagreements at a distance?</string>
    <string name="ad_93">What could I do to help you feel more understood during conflicts?</string>
    <string name="ad_94">What have you discovered new about me since the beginning of our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ad_95">Would you be comfortable talking about how we\'d like to handle conflicts once we\'re together?</string>
    <string name="ad_96">When did you feel that our bond is truly special?</string>
    <string name="ad_97">What would you like me to repeat to you more often?</string>
    <string name="ad_98">If we wrote a book about our love, what would its title be?</string>
    <string name="ad_99">What voice message from me has stayed with you the most?</string>
    <string name="add_1_favorite">Add 1 favorite</string>
    <string name="add_5_favorites">Add 5 favorites</string>
    <string name="add_journal_events">Add memories to your journal</string>
    <string name="add_photo">Add photo</string>
    <string name="add_profile_photo">Add profile photo</string>
    <string name="add_relationship_date">Add your relationship start date in settings</string>
    <string name="add_to_favorites">Add to favorites</string>
    <string name="add_widgets">Add your widgets</string>
    <string name="all_completed">All completed</string>
    <string name="already_have_account">I already have an account</string>
    <string name="always_authorized">Always authorized</string>
    <string name="and_conjunction">and</string>
    <string name="and_others">and</string>
    <string name="app_description">Deepen your bond through fun and intimate questions.</string>
    <string name="app_name">Love2Love</string>
    <string name="app_tagline">The app that brings you closer</string>
    <string name="app_version">1.86</string>
    <string name="authentication_error">Authentication error</string>
    <string name="authentication_in_progress">Authentication in progress</string>
    <string name="authentication_required">Apple authentication required</string>
    <string name="authorize_button">Authorize</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="both_have_access">Both have access</string>
    <string name="cache_clear_confirmation">This action will delete all cached questions. They will be automatically reloaded on next use.</string>
    <string name="cache_size">Cache size</string>
    <string name="calendar_friday">FRI</string>
    <string name="calendar_monday">MON</string>
    <string name="calendar_saturday">SAT</string>
    <string name="calendar_sunday">SUN</string>
    <string name="calendar_thursday">THU</string>
    <string name="calendar_tuesday">TUE</string>
    <string name="calendar_wednesday">WED</string>
    <string name="can_request_review">Can request review:</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cancel_subscription">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cannot_read_receipt">Cannot read purchase receipt</string>
    <string name="cant_wait_to_see_you">I can\'t wait to see you</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="category_a_distance_subtitle">Far from the eyes, close to the heart.</string>
    <string name="category_a_distance_title">Long Distance Relationship</string>
    <string name="category_desirs_inavoues_subtitle">Share your desires and discover each other more deeply.</string>
    <string name="category_desirs_inavoues_title">Hidden Desires</string>
    <string name="category_en_couple_subtitle">Questions to remember what unites us.</string>
    <string name="category_en_couple_title">You and Me</string>
    <string name="category_mieux_ensemble_subtitle">Loving also means learning to heal.</string>
    <string name="category_mieux_ensemble_title">Healing Our Love</string>
    <string name="category_pour_rire_subtitle">Because love also means laughing together.</string>
    <string name="category_pour_rire_title">Laugh Together</string>
    <string name="category_pour_un_date_subtitle">Questions to see each other beyond appearances.</string>
    <string name="category_pour_un_date_title">On a Date</string>
    <string name="category_questions_profondes_subtitle">Discover the thoughts you donâ€™t always say out loud.</string>
    <string name="category_questions_profondes_title">Deep Questions</string>
    <string name="category_tu_preferes_subtitle">Questions that reveal what really matters to you.</string>
    <string name="category_tu_preferes_title">Would you rather?</string>
    <string name="challenge_completed_button">Complete challenge</string>
    <string name="challenge_completed">Challenge completed!</string>
    <string name="challenge_mark_done">Mark as done</string>
    <string name="challenge_save">Save</string>
    <string name="challenge_saved">Challenge saved!</string>
    <string name="challenge_saved_confirmation">Challenge saved!</string>
    <string name="choose_date">Choose date</string>
    <string name="choose_location">Choose location</string>
    <string name="choose_photo">Choose photo</string>
    <string name="choose_plan">Choose your plan</string>
    <string name="choose_time">Choose time</string>
    <string name="cities">cities</string>
    <string name="cities_visited">Cities\nvisited</string>
    <string name="city">city</string>
    <string name="clean_orphan_codes">ðŸ§¹ Clean orphan codes</string>
    <string name="clear_cache">Clear cache</string>
    <string name="code_generation">Code generation...</string>
    <string name="come_back_tomorrow_challenge">Come back tomorrow to discover a new challenge!</string>
    <string name="communication_evaluation_question">On a scale of 1 to 10, how would you rate the communication in your relationship?</string>
    <string name="complete_guide">Complete guide</string>
    <string name="complicity_need_help">We need help</string>
    <string name="complicity_present">Present</string>
    <string name="complicity_question">How would you describe your complicity in your relationship today?</string>
    <string name="complicity_sometimes_lacking">Sometimes lacking</string>
    <string name="complicity_strong_fulfilling">Strong and fulfilling</string>
    <string name="confidence_completely">Yes, completely</string>
    <string name="confidence_most_of_time">Most of the time</string>
    <string name="confidence_not_always">Not always</string>
    <string name="confidence_question">Would you say you feel completely confident being yourself with your partner?</string>
    <string name="congratulations">Congratulations</string>
    <string name="congratulations_pack">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="connect_partner_button">Connect my partner</string>
    <string name="connect_partner_description">Connect with your partner to share your journal with them, and enjoy all the app\'s features.</string>
    <string name="connect_with_partner">Connect with your partner</string>
    <string name="connected_on">Connected on</string>
    <string name="connected_with">Connected with %@</string>
    <string name="connected_with_partner">You are connected ðŸ’ž</string>
    <string name="connecting">Connecting...</string>
    <string name="connecting_status">Connecting...</string>
    <string name="connection_error">Connection error</string>
    <string name="connection_successful">Connection successful!</string>
    <string name="connection_successful_status">Connection successful...</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="continue_anyway">Continue anyway</string>
    <string name="continue_free_version">Continue with free version</string>
    <string name="continue_special">Continue</string>
    <string name="continue_with_apple">Continue with Apple</string>
    <string name="continue_with_google">Continue with Google</string>
    <string name="continue_as_guest">Continue as Guest</string>
    <string name="continue_without_notifications_button">Continue without notifications</string>
    <string name="countdown_timer">Countdown timer</string>
    <string name="countries">countries</string>
    <string name="countries_visited">Countries\nvisited</string>
    <string name="country">country</string>
    <string name="couple_statistics">Your couple statistics</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create account</string>
    <string name="create_account_description">Create an account to keep your activity history and easily find your favorite conversations anytime!</string>
    <string name="create_memory_card">Create your memory map</string>
    <string name="create_secure_account">Create your account and secure your data</string>
    <string name="created_by">Created by</string>
    <string name="crop_photo_instructions">Adjust your profile photo</string>
    <string name="current_status">Current status:</string>
    <string name="current_user">ðŸ‘¤ Current User</string>
    <string name="custom_location">Custom location</string>
    <string name="customize_description">Tap â€˜Customize\' to set up your widgets.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_1">Send them a message telling them why you\'re grateful to have them in your life.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_10">Create together a list of 10 things you love doing together.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_11">Compliment them on something they don\'t notice about themselves.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_12">Teach them something you know how to do.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_13">Before going to bed, end the day with 3 \"I love you\"s, each in a different tone or form.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_14">Write a digital love letter and send it by email.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_15">Have a video call and eat the same meal at the same time.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_16">Exchange a voice message that starts with: \"I wanted to tell youâ€¦\"</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_17">Make a call where you only speak in another language (even clumsily) to laugh together.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_18">Send a video where you tell them how you feel today.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_19">Send a photo of your hand with a heart drawn on it and their name inside.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_2">Call them on FaceTime or phone just to say \"I love you\" and hang up right after their response.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_20">Tell them a quality they underestimate about themselves.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_21">Offer them a surprise remote order (UberEats, Amazonâ€¦). (but be careful not to exceed â‚¬12, be creative)</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_22">Send a photo of a place where you\'d like to be together.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_23">Send a 100% physical compliment, then a 100% inner one.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_24">Each answer this question: \"How do you know that I love you?\"</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_25">Draw an animal that represents your partner and send it to them.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_26">Describe your partner in 3 hashtags and share them.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_27">Create together a golden rule for your relationship, something you\'ll never want to break.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_28">Mix your name with theirs to create a duo name (like a band name or cocktail).</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_29">Each create a \"magic love potion\" with ingredients like \"3 tears of laughter\", \"5 pinches of kisses\", etc.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_3">Ask them this question: \"What do you need from me right now?\"</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_30">Record a voice message speaking like a wildlife documentary narrator describing your partner.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_31">Imagine what a perfect day would look like if you were both 6-year-old kids together.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_32">Tell the story of your first kiss (or first special moment) as if you were old and nostalgic.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_33">Each choose a fruit to symbolize your partner and explain why you picked it.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_34">Create a rule for the \"world order of lovers\" that all couples should follow to be happy.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_35">Call each other by a cartoon character name of your choice for the whole day.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_36">Each choose a color that represents your partner and explain why.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_37">Create an \"imaginary perfect day\" with an hour-by-hour schedule of what you\'d do together.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_38">Create a phrase to recite whenever you have doubts or during disagreements.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_39">Send a \"mirror voice note\": tell your love what you\'d like to hear today.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_4">Choose a song that reminds you of your relationship and send it to them.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_40">Draw a heart with your partner\'s name inside and send them the photo.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_41">Give each other a unique nickname to use just for today.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_42">Have a 2-minute video call without talking - just stare at each other. First one to look away or laugh loses!</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_43">Ask your partner: If I could surprise you right now, what would you want?</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_44">Write a sentence to your partner that you wish someone had told you when you were a child.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_45">Send each other \"I love you\" in a foreign language you don\'t speak.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_46">Find 2 topics you\'ve never discussed together and talk about them tonight.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_47">Write down three things you admire about each other and read them out loud.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_48">Create a fictional memory together as if you actually lived it.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_49">Create a rule for the day (like: no saying \"no\", or starting every sentence with \"my love\"...).</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_5">Create together a list of 5 things you want to do as a couple.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_50">Send them a photo of a place where you\'d love to go together.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_51">Imitate your partner\'s voice in an audio message (lovingly) and send it using their vocabulary.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_52">Write a Tinder bio for each other and share them.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_53">Exchange a message written with your \"non-dominant hand\" (left hand if you\'re right-handed).</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_6">Set an alarm to remind yourself to send them \"I love you\" during the day.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_7">Take a photo of something that reminds you of your partner and send it to them.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_8">Give them an affectionate nickname just for today.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_9">Ask them a question you\'ve never asked them before.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_intro_subtitle">Every day, a new challenge to strengthen your bond and grow your relationship through meaningful shared actions.\nConnect to start the journey together.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_intro_title">Take on every challenge together ðŸŽ¯</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_no_partner_title">Partner Required</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_no_partner_message">You need to connect with your partner to access daily challenges.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_preparing">Preparingâ€¦</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_preparing_subtitle">We are preparing your challenge</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_subtitle_multiple_days_remaining">âœ¨ %d free days remaining â€¢ Then subscription required</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_subtitle_one_day_remaining">âœ¨ 1 free day remaining â€¢ Then subscription required</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_subtitle_subscribed">ðŸ’Ž Included with your Premium subscription</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_subtitle_subscription_required">ðŸ”’ Subscription required to continue</string>
    <string name="daily_challenges_title">Daily Challenge</string>
    <string name="daily_question_1">What didnâ€™t you receive enough of in your past relationships that youâ€™d love to experience with me?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_10">Where do you see us in five years, and what steps can we take today to make that vision a reality?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_11">What would you love to receive more of from me, that youâ€™re not getting enough of right now? I promise Iâ€™ll try my best to give it to you.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_12">Tell me the most beautiful thing Iâ€™ve ever done for you and why it meant so much to you.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_13">Whatâ€™s your absolute favorite thing to do with me?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_14">If we had to express gratitude to each other for one thing, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_15">What kind of gift do you love receiving most from me?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_16">Is there a part of your personality youâ€™ve been hiding from me because youâ€™re afraid of being judged?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_17">Is there something I do that bothers you â€” and that you wish Iâ€™d stop doing? Help me understand why you think itâ€™s a barrier to our love, or why it could become one.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_18">Is there something about your past or your childhood that you havenâ€™t shared with me yet, but would like to talk about?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_19">If you had to describe my love language, what would you say it is?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_2">What kind of behavior would make you walk away from a relationship? And how can we make sure that never happens between us?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_20">What is our greatest strength as a couple?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_21">Is there something I take lightly that you take very seriously?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_22">Do you feel like I take enough time to truly get to know you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_23">When we argue, what could I change in the way I react?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_24">If our love went through a tough time, what would you want me to never forget to do for you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_25">What version of yourself would you like to become by my side, and how can I support you on that path?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_26">Is there an emotional need I don\'t see enough in you, but that you wish I understood better?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_27">What would you like me to notice more about you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_28">What do I do well that you\'d like me to keep doing, even years from now?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_29">When you doubt yourself, what can I do or say to help you feel confident again?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_3">Whatâ€™s something you wish I would ask you more often?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_30">Is there a simple gesture I could do more often that would have a big impact on your well-being?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_31">Is there a side of you you\'d like to show me more, but don\'t fully dare to yet?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_32">If I had to improve in one area of our relationship, which one would you choose first?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_33">What would you like me to see in you, even when you don\'t have the strength to show it?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_34">Is there a way you\'d like me to talk to you more often?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_35">When I make a decision, do you feel like I consider you enough in it?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_36">What would you like me to do more spontaneously, without you having to ask?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_37">Do you feel like I put in enough effort to build something solid with you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_38">When we disagree, do you still feel respected in your opinions?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_39">What do you miss the most when we don\'t see each other for a few days?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_4">Is there something youâ€™re hoping for from me, but havenâ€™t dared to ask yet?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_40">Do you think we laugh enough together?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_41">Do you feel like we\'re moving in the same direction together?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_42">When you\'re having a bad day, do you feel like I respond the way you need me to?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_43">Is there a topic we avoid too often that we should actually talk about?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_44">Do you feel like I consider your opinion when I make important decisions?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_45">When we disagree, do you feel like I genuinely try to understand you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_46">Do you feel like we\'re building a relationship that can truly last? If yes, why? If not, what should we change?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_47">Do we enjoy simple things together enough?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_48">Is there something I do well, but not often enough?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_49">Do you think I adapt well enough to the way you function?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_5">What emotional wound from your past are you still trying to heal? And how can I help you in that process?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_50">Do you feel like I truly listen when you talk about things that matter to you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_51">What would you like me to value more in you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_6">What is the one quality you love most about me, and never want to see change?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_7">What small daily gesture could we do for each other to bring more joy into our everyday life?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_8">If you had to suggest three ideas to help us better handle conflicts, what would they be?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_9">Do you feel our relationship is balanced when it comes to giving and receiving? If not, how can we improve that?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_benefits_description">Every day, you and your partner will receive a question specially designed to improve your relationship quality and strengthen your bond.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_benefits_title">Daily connection, stronger bond</string>
    <string name="daily_question_couples_only">Available only for connected couples</string>
    <string name="daily_question_example_header">Daily Question</string>
    <string name="daily_question_example_text">What do you think we should prioritize to improve our relationship?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_intro_subtitle">Every day, discover a unique question specially designed to strengthen your bond, deepen your love, and nurture the connection between you.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_intro_time">Every day at 9 PM</string>
    <string name="daily_question_intro_title">A daily love ritual</string>
    <string name="daily_question_loading">Loading question...</string>
    <string name="daily_question_no_partner_message">You need to connect with your partner to access daily questions.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_no_partner_title">Partner Required</string>
    <string name="daily_question_notification_title">ðŸ’• Daily Question</string>
    <string name="daily_question_onboarding_title">Answer the question of the day</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_encouragement">The magic happens when you\'re both ready to connect ðŸ’•</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_notification_subtitle">Ask %@ to activate notifications to unlock daily questions together.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_notification_title">Almost ready!</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_ready_button">My partner is ready</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_refresh_note">This page will refresh automatically once your partner activates notifications</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_step_1">Share this feature with your partner</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_step_2">Ask them to activate notifications</string>
    <string name="daily_question_partner_step_3">Start your daily love ritual together</string>
    <string name="daily_question_permission_subtitle">Every day, you and your partner will receive a question specially designed to improve the quality of your relationship and strengthen the bond that unites you.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_permission_title">Notifications are required to unlock daily questions</string>
    <string name="daily_question_preparing">Preparingâ€¦</string>
    <string name="daily_question_preparing_subtitle">We are preparing your chat space</string>
    <string name="daily_question_preview_header">Preview</string>
    <string name="daily_question_preview_text">What do you think we should prioritize to improve our relationship?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_response_placeholder">Share your thoughts...</string>
    <string name="daily_question_start_conversation">Start the conversation by sharing your answer.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_submit_response">Send</string>
    <string name="daily_question_subtitle_multiple_days_remaining">âœ¨ %d free days remaining â€¢ Then subscription required</string>
    <string name="daily_question_subtitle_one_day_remaining">âœ¨ 1 free day remaining â€¢ Then subscription required</string>
    <string name="daily_question_subtitle_subscribed">ðŸ’Ž Included with your Premium subscription</string>
    <string name="daily_question_subtitle_subscription_required">ðŸ”’ Subscription required to continue</string>
    <string name="daily_question_title">Question of the Day</string>
    <string name="daily_question_type_response">Type your response...</string>
    <string name="daily_question_send_button">Send</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_all_completed">Congratulations! You\'ve answered all daily questions.</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_answered">Questions answered</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_available">Daily questions available</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_completion">Completion rate</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_congratulations">Congratulations on strengthening your relationship through meaningful conversations!</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_exhausted_message">You\'ve completed all daily questions! Your conversation history remains accessible below.</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_exhausted_stats">Questions completed: %d/%d</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_exhausted_stats_simple">All questions completed!</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_exhausted_title">Journey Complete!</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_new_cycle">New questions will start from the beginning.</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_streak">Current streak</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_total">Total questions</string>
    <string name="daily_questions_view_history">View Full History</string>
    <string name="dash_placeholder">----</string>
    <string name="dash_separator">--</string>
    <string name="days">days</string>
    <string name="days_before_anniversary">days before your next anniversary</string>
    <string name="days_plural">days</string>
    <string name="days_singular">day</string>
    <string name="days_together">Days\ntogether</string>
    <string name="debug_review_system">Debug Review System</string>
    <string name="debug_sync_subscriptions">Debug - Sync Subscriptions</string>
    <string name="default_love_message">Thinking of you</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_description">General notifications from Love2Love</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">default_channel</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name">Love2Love Notifications</string>
    <string name="delete_challenge_button">Supprimer le dÃ©fi</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="disconnect_confirmation">Are you sure you want to disconnect from your partner? This action will remove data sharing.</string>
    <string name="discover_premium">Discover Premium</string>
    <string name="discovery_time_could_do_better">We could do better</string>
    <string name="discovery_time_no">No</string>
    <string name="discovery_time_question">Do you think you take enough time in your relationship to truly discover each other?</string>
    <string name="discovery_time_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="display_name_placeholder">How your partner will see you</string>
    <string name="display_name_step_title">Choose your nickname</string>
    <string name="distance">distance</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="ec_1">Do you feel like you can be completely honest with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_10">What little things make you feel deeply loved by me?</string>
    <string name="ec_100">Do you find me grateful enough?</string>
    <string name="ec_101">Who takes more risks between you and me?</string>
    <string name="ec_102">What are the most important values for you in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_103">If a movie were made about your life, which actor would you choose to play your role?</string>
    <string name="ec_104">Would you like me to listen to you a bit more?</string>
    <string name="ec_105">How do you feel when we disagree?</string>
    <string name="ec_106">Is there something from your romantic past that still influences our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_107">What is something you don\'t like doing but do for me?</string>
    <string name="ec_108">Do you consider yourself optimistic or pessimistic?</string>
    <string name="ec_109">Do you believe everything happens for a reason?</string>
    <string name="ec_11">Is there something you\'d need more of from me emotionally?</string>
    <string name="ec_110">What is something you\'re afraid to tell me?</string>
    <string name="ec_111">Do you have physical complexes that affect your confidence in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_112">Are there moments in our relationship when you feel uncertain or unsure about what I feel for you?</string>
    <string name="ec_113">Have you ever felt not good enough for me or thought I deserved better?</string>
    <string name="ec_114">What surprised you most about our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_115">Are you afraid our differences might become a problem in the future?</string>
    <string name="ec_116">What would you like me to understand about your way of loving, deep down?</string>
    <string name="ec_117">What role would you like to have in our relationship in 10 years?</string>
    <string name="ec_118">Do you like my love language?</string>
    <string name="ec_119">Is there a secret or something unsaid you\'d like to reveal to me someday?</string>
    <string name="ec_12">What is your biggest fear for our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_120">If you knew everything you know today, would you still choose me?</string>
    <string name="ec_121">What do you feel when I\'m not doing well?</string>
    <string name="ec_122">Was there a moment when you didn\'t feel heard by me?</string>
    <string name="ec_123">What is the biggest misunderstanding we\'ve had according to you?</string>
    <string name="ec_124">What have you learned about love thanks to me?</string>
    <string name="ec_125">What past wound would you like me to know better to understand you?</string>
    <string name="ec_126">What do you feel when I succeed or have success?</string>
    <string name="ec_127">What is one of the most difficult experiences you\'ve been through?</string>
    <string name="ec_128">Are there topics you voluntarily avoid with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_129">How has your past influenced your way of communicating with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_13">What do you appreciate about the way we communicate?</string>
    <string name="ec_130">What has been the biggest change in your life since we\'ve been together?</string>
    <string name="ec_131">Are there specific things you\'d like me to be attentive to because of what you\'ve experienced?</string>
    <string name="ec_132">How would you define the balance between giving and receiving in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_133">Have you ever found yourself unable to fully trust me because of your past? Do you think we could talk about it?</string>
    <string name="ec_134">What do you want to preserve at all costs between us?</string>
    <string name="ec_135">What is your greatest hope for our future?</string>
    <string name="ec_136">What makes you sometimes doubt us?</string>
    <string name="ec_137">What is something you only do with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_138">What is the most beautiful sacrifice you\'ve made out of love for me?</string>
    <string name="ec_139">Is there a part of your personality you hide for fear I won\'t love you anymore?</string>
    <string name="ec_14">If you could relive one moment with me, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="ec_140">What is the emotion you have the most trouble sharing with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_141">How has your upbringing influenced your vision of love and relationships?</string>
    <string name="ec_142">What importance do you place on honesty and communication in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_143">Do you believe in forgiveness in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_144">What sometimes holds you back in our communication?</string>
    <string name="ec_145">Do you think it\'s healthy to have separate interests in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_146">Do you think we should spend a bit more time apart to miss each other better?</string>
    <string name="ec_147">Where do you see our relationship in five years?</string>
    <string name="ec_148">Is there a difficult truth you\'d like to hear from me, even if it hurts?</string>
    <string name="ec_149">What have you never told me because you didn\'t know how to phrase it?</string>
    <string name="ec_15">What makes you proud of us?</string>
    <string name="ec_150">What is something you\'d like us to do more often as a couple?</string>
    <string name="ec_151">What do you appreciate about our relationship but have never told me before?</string>
    <string name="ec_152">Are there qualities in you that you\'d like me to validate more?</string>
    <string name="ec_153">What new thing would you like to try in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_154">How could we better support each other in our personal goals?</string>
    <string name="ec_155">What would be a meaningful way to celebrate the major milestones of our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_156">Are there words I say that affect you more than I realize?</string>
    <string name="ec_157">What is the most important thing to say but we don\'t say often enough?</string>
    <string name="ec_158">What is a new way we could express our love and appreciation for each other?</string>
    <string name="ec_159">What is something you\'d like me to notice more often about you?</string>
    <string name="ec_16">Is there something you hesitate to tell me about your family?</string>
    <string name="ec_160">Is there a gesture or phrase that hurt you that we never talked about again?</string>
    <string name="ec_161">What is a song that instantly reminds you of a special moment we shared?</string>
    <string name="ec_162">What does vulnerability mean to you in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_163">If we had to be locked in a store for one night, which would we choose?</string>
    <string name="ec_164">Is there something you regret not telling me earlier?</string>
    <string name="ec_165">How do you feel when you don\'t hear from me for a while?</string>
    <string name="ec_166">What is something you think about often, but keep to yourself?</string>
    <string name="ec_167">How do you want us to support each other in our moments of weakness?</string>
    <string name="ec_168">If I could make one fear or doubt in you disappear, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="ec_169">If we had to put a label on our relationship, what would it say?</string>
    <string name="ec_17">What would you like to improve in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_170">What aspect of your personality would you like me to accept more?</string>
    <string name="ec_171">How is our relationship different from your parents\'?</string>
    <string name="ec_172">Is there something you feel but don\'t want to impose on me?</string>
    <string name="ec_173">How do you think we balance each other out?</string>
    <string name="ec_174">What is your favorite way to relax after a long day?</string>
    <string name="ec_175">What helps you forgive when I hurt you?</string>
    <string name="ec_176">If we could create a new romantic tradition, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="ec_177">What do you secretly love about our routine?</string>
    <string name="ec_178">Is there something you\'re afraid to tell me for fear of my reaction?</string>
    <string name="ec_179">What is something you\'d never want me to trivialize in your life?</string>
    <string name="ec_18">What do you feel when we hold each other?</string>
    <string name="ec_180">What is something silly we should do at least once just for the story?</string>
    <string name="ec_181">If we had to summarize our love story in three emojis, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="ec_182">If we had to invent a challenge for each other, what would you suggest?</string>
    <string name="ec_183">If we had to get matching tattoos, what design would we choose?</string>
    <string name="ec_184">If we had to summarize our love story in one sentence, what would it say?</string>
    <string name="ec_185">What is the compliment from me you\'ll never forget?</string>
    <string name="ec_186">If we created a memory jar, what would be the first thing we\'d write on a little paper?</string>
    <string name="ec_187">If we made a playlist for a road trip, what would be the first song we\'d put on it?</string>
    <string name="ec_188">When did you feel like we formed a real team?</string>
    <string name="ec_189">If we had to write each other\'s dating profile, what would you put in it?</string>
    <string name="ec_19">Is there a habit of mine that you find adorable?</string>
    <string name="ec_190">If we could relive one perfect day of our relationship, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="ec_191">Do you feel like we spend enough time together?</string>
    <string name="ec_192">Is there something bothering you right now that we haven\'t talked about yet?</string>
    <string name="ec_193">What are the things I\'ve done this month (or this week) that you appreciated or that made you feel loved?</string>
    <string name="ec_194">What would you like us to work on together?</string>
    <string name="ec_195">What is your favorite way to receive love in my gestures?</string>
    <string name="ec_196">Are there new experiences you\'d like to have with me soon?</string>
    <string name="ec_197">What are your personal goals for this month, and how can I help you achieve them?</string>
    <string name="ec_198">What would you like me to protect in you, even when you doubt?</string>
    <string name="ec_199">What memory of us would you like to relive once more?</string>
    <string name="ec_2">Is there something you\'d like to do as a couple that we haven\'t done yet?</string>
    <string name="ec_20">When did you know you were in love?</string>
    <string name="ec_200">Is there something you need that I\'m not giving you right now?</string>
    <string name="ec_201">When did you feel like I really understood you without you saying a word?</string>
    <string name="ec_202">What can I do to make your days more pleasant or easier?</string>
    <string name="ec_203">Is there a moment in our relationship that you sometimes relive in your thoughts?</string>
    <string name="ec_204">How could I better respond to your emotional needs?</string>
    <string name="ec_205">If we could talk to each other without filter, what would you want us to talk about today?</string>
    <string name="ec_206">What am I doing right now that you particularly love or appreciate?</string>
    <string name="ec_207">What are, according to you, my biggest areas for improvement?</string>
    <string name="ec_208">Is there something I used to do at the beginning of our relationship that I don\'t do as much anymore, that you\'d like to see return?</string>
    <string name="ec_209">Do you think I take you for granted?</string>
    <string name="ec_21">If we wrote a book about our story, what would the title be?</string>
    <string name="ec_210">Is there something stressful in your life right now that I should know about?</string>
    <string name="ec_211">Have you felt generally happy lately?</string>
    <string name="ec_212">How can I better support your personal growth?</string>
    <string name="ec_213">Is there something you\'d like us to do differently or try in our intimacy?</string>
    <string name="ec_214">What would you like us to say to each other more often?</string>
    <string name="ec_215">What are you looking forward to this week / this month?</string>
    <string name="ec_216">If we had to reinvent ourselves as a couple, what would you absolutely keep?</string>
    <string name="ec_217">Is there a promise you\'d like us to make to each other?</string>
    <string name="ec_218">Would you like us to talk about our future goals? Are there things to update, adjust or discuss?</string>
    <string name="ec_219">What are ways we could have more fun together in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_22">What song makes you think of us?</string>
    <string name="ec_220">Is there something I do that pushes you away without me realizing it?</string>
    <string name="ec_221">If our relationship were a quote, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="ec_222">When do you feel like our relationship is growing?</string>
    <string name="ec_223">Are there important dates coming up that I should know about?</string>
    <string name="ec_224">Do you think we share the same vision of our future?</string>
    <string name="ec_225">What attracts you most about me?</string>
    <string name="ec_226">If you could choose one word to symbolize our relationship, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="ec_227">Is there a conflict we never really resolved according to you?</string>
    <string name="ec_228">What do you think is one of my best qualities?</string>
    <string name="ec_229">What is the first thing you noticed about me?</string>
    <string name="ec_23">Do you think we mutually support each other\'s dreams?</string>
    <string name="ec_230">If our relationship were a work of art, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="ec_231">What would be the ideal place for you to retire?</string>
    <string name="ec_232">What overcome difficulty in our relationship strengthened your love for me?</string>
    <string name="ec_233">What would an ideal date look like according to you?</string>
    <string name="ec_234">What part of your story would you like me to know better?</string>
    <string name="ec_235">What helps you stay committed to our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_236">What is the number one thing on your dream gift list?</string>
    <string name="ec_237">Is there something about me you\'d like to be able to change?</string>
    <string name="ec_238">Are you happy in this relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_239">What is the most beautiful thing our relationship has revealed to you about yourself?</string>
    <string name="ec_24">What small gesture from me touches you the most?</string>
    <string name="ec_240">How do you want us to love each other in 10 years?</string>
    <string name="ec_241">Do you think our relationship is moving in the right direction?</string>
    <string name="ec_242">What small daily ritual would strengthen our bond?</string>
    <string name="ec_243">Are there boundaries you\'d like to set?</string>
    <string name="ec_244">If you could confide one thing to me without fear of being judged, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="ec_245">What importance do you place on forgiveness in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_246">How do our personalities complement each other?</string>
    <string name="ec_247">What legacy would you like us to build together?</string>
    <string name="ec_248">Do you believe we were meant to be together?</string>
    <string name="ec_249">What do you think will be the biggest challenges we\'ll have to face in our shared future?</string>
    <string name="ec_25">What is your definition of a happy couple?</string>
    <string name="ec_250">What does being a good partner mean to you?</string>
    <string name="ec_251">How do you like to make peace after an argument?</string>
    <string name="ec_252">What do you think is the most important thing for a long-term relationship to work?</string>
    <string name="ec_253">How could we strengthen trust between us?</string>
    <string name="ec_254">Name 3 things you\'re grateful for regarding me</string>
    <string name="ec_255">Can you tell me you love me right now?</string>
    <string name="ec_256">Is there anything else you\'d like us to talk about?</string>
    <string name="ec_26">Do you feel like we have enough fun together?</string>
    <string name="ec_27">What has our relationship taught you about yourself?</string>
    <string name="ec_28">Do you have a romantic fantasy you\'d like to share with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_29">Is there a part of your past you\'re afraid to share with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_3">Is there a topic you feel we don\'t talk about enough?</string>
    <string name="ec_30">What do you think about how we manage our social life as a couple?</string>
    <string name="ec_31">What is the most beautiful proof of love you\'ve received from me?</string>
    <string name="ec_32">What is your favorite moment of our daily routine together?</string>
    <string name="ec_33">What would you like me to understand better about you?</string>
    <string name="ec_34">If we made a promise today, which would be the most important to you?</string>
    <string name="ec_35">Do you sometimes feel like I\'m not listening to you?</string>
    <string name="ec_36">Is there something you\'d like to do as a couple that we haven\'t done yet?</string>
    <string name="ec_37">What is the most beautiful compliment you\'ve received from me?</string>
    <string name="ec_38">If you had to describe me to a stranger, what would you say?</string>
    <string name="ec_39">What would you like us to try together to break out of routine?</string>
    <string name="ec_4">Do you feel like we\'re growing together or growing apart?</string>
    <string name="ec_40">Is there a difficult moment we went through together that you\'re proud of?</string>
    <string name="ec_41">What do you find most beautiful about our story?</string>
    <string name="ec_42">What is something you think we don\'t talk about enough?</string>
    <string name="ec_43">Do you feel like we have enough deep conversations?</string>
    <string name="ec_44">Is there something you\'re afraid of losing by being in this relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_45">What is something you think we need to work on as a couple?</string>
    <string name="ec_46">What new couple habit would you like us to establish?</string>
    <string name="ec_47">Is there something you\'d like to dare to tell me but never have?</string>
    <string name="ec_48">Do you feel like our relationship is balanced between what we give and receive?</string>
    <string name="ec_49">What is something you\'d like me to change about myself?</string>
    <string name="ec_5">What fears do you have when you think about our future?</string>
    <string name="ec_50">What gesture or word gives you confidence in our love again?</string>
    <string name="ec_51">Is there a movie or series that makes you think of our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_52">What would you like us to build together in the coming year?</string>
    <string name="ec_53">Is there something I do that makes you feel unloved?</string>
    <string name="ec_54">What are the little daily things that nourish our love?</string>
    <string name="ec_55">How do you feel about our future together?</string>
    <string name="ec_56">What would you like me to understand without you having to say a word?</string>
    <string name="ec_57">What is your vision of a fulfilled long-term couple?</string>
    <string name="ec_58">What question would you like me to ask you more often?</string>
    <string name="ec_59">What is the most beautiful gift you\'d like to receive from me (non-material)?</string>
    <string name="ec_6">Do you feel truly heard and understood in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_60">If we had a whole day without any constraints, what would you want us to do?</string>
    <string name="ec_61">How do you know I love you, even when I don\'t say it?</string>
    <string name="ec_62">What is a bad habit I have that affects our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_63">Do you sometimes feel like you can\'t be yourself with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_64">Is there a way I could support you better in your personal goals?</string>
    <string name="ec_65">What do you love about how we take care of each other?</string>
    <string name="ec_66">What is the most beautiful romantic moment we\'ve shared together?</string>
    <string name="ec_67">How could I make you feel even more loved?</string>
    <string name="ec_68">How do you feel about the current state of our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_69">How loved and appreciated do you feel by me, truly?</string>
    <string name="ec_7">What kind of words or gestures from me would truly comfort you?</string>
    <string name="ec_70">What are your expectations of me?</string>
    <string name="ec_71">What do you love most about our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_72">What activities do you prefer to do with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_73">Realistically, how do you see our future together?</string>
    <string name="ec_74">What are your dreams and goals for us as a couple?</string>
    <string name="ec_75">What would you like us to do more often together?</string>
    <string name="ec_76">What do you think is our greatest strength as a couple?</string>
    <string name="ec_77">What is your most beautiful memory of our first date?</string>
    <string name="ec_78">If you had to define our relationship in three words, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="ec_79">What makes our relationship unique in your eyes?</string>
    <string name="ec_8">Do you feel like something is missing in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_80">Is there a trip we haven\'t taken yet but you dream of taking with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_81">How would you spend an ideal weekend with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_82">Do you think infidelity is always a point of no return, regardless of circumstances?</string>
    <string name="ec_83">What part of me do you find most beautiful (physically or internally)?</string>
    <string name="ec_84">Is there a gesture from me you\'d like to become a little ritual between us?</string>
    <string name="ec_85">What do you want to protect at all costs in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="ec_86">What place does humor take in our relationship according to you?</string>
    <string name="ec_87">Who is more inclined to trust, you or me?</string>
    <string name="ec_88">What makes you happiest when we\'re together?</string>
    <string name="ec_89">What part of our daily routine seems magical to you, even if it\'s simple?</string>
    <string name="ec_9">What strength or character trait in me inspires you the most?</string>
    <string name="ec_90">If our love were a color, what would it be and why?</string>
    <string name="ec_91">Who is more likely to be jealous, you or me?</string>
    <string name="ec_92">What advice would you give to a couple just starting out, based on our experience?</string>
    <string name="ec_93">Is there a moment with me you\'d like to engrave forever?</string>
    <string name="ec_94">What is the first thing you found attractive about me?</string>
    <string name="ec_95">What has our relationship overcome that you\'re proud of?</string>
    <string name="ec_96">How do you hide your anger when you don\'t want to show it?</string>
    <string name="ec_97">What do you feel when you think about me?</string>
    <string name="ec_98">What would you like to learn from me or with me?</string>
    <string name="ec_99">What is a little thing you do for me without me realizing it?</string>
    <string name="ellipsis">...</string>
    <string name="empty_journal_message">Your memory journal is empty</string>
    <string name="enjoy_it">Enjoy!</string>
    <string name="enter_code">Enter code</string>
    <string name="enter_code_placeholder">Enter the code</string>
    <string name="enter_partner_code">Enter your partner\'s code</string>
    <string name="entry_creation_error">Entry creation error</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="event_date">Event date</string>
    <string name="event_date_picker">Event date</string>
    <string name="event_time">Time</string>
    <string name="events_count">events</string>
    <string name="events_of_date">Events of</string>
    <string name="exclamation">!</string>
    <string name="exclusive_premium_content">Exclusive premium content</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="favorites_count">Favorites:</string>
    <string name="favorites_counter">of</string>
    <string name="feature_love_map">âœ“ A new challenge every day</string>
    <string name="feature_love_map_description">Receive a romantic challenge every day to grow closer, even from afar.</string>
    <string name="feature_love_stronger">âœ“ To love each other even stronger</string>
    <string name="feature_love_stronger_description">Unlock over 1,800 questions specially designed to bring you closer, discover facets of your partner you don\'t know yet, and above all establish healthy and sincere communication between you two.</string>
    <string name="feature_memory_chest">âœ“ Keep your best memories in one place</string>
    <string name="feature_memory_chest_description">Because every moment deserves a special place. Keep your most beautiful memories in a shared journal made just for the two of you.</string>
    <string name="feel_closer_partner">To feel even closer to your partner.</string>
    <string name="for_2_users"> for 2 users</string>
    <string name="for_surprise">for a</string>
    <string name="free_entries">entry</string>
    <string name="free_entries_plural">entries</string>
    <string name="free_text">free</string>
    <string name="free_text_plural">free</string>
    <string name="freemium_check_failed">Limit check error</string>
    <string name="freemium_limit_reached">Free entries limit reached</string>
    <string name="gallery_access_error">Gallery access error</string>
    <string name="gallery_access_required">Gallery access is required to add a photo. Please enable it in your device settings.</string>
    <string name="generate_question">Generate a question</string>
    <string name="generating">Generating...</string>
    <string name="generation_error">Generation error</string>
    <string name="generic_partner">your partner</string>
    <string name="get_premium">Get Premium</string>
    <string name="goal_create_connection">Build a deeper connection</string>
    <string name="goal_find_complicity">Feel close again, like before</string>
    <string name="goal_increase_passion">Increase the passion between us</string>
    <string name="goal_share_more_laughs">Share more laughs together</string>
    <string name="goal_talk_avoided_subjects">Talk about what we usually avoid</string>
    <string name="happy_anniversary">Happy anniversary! ðŸŽ‰</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="home_screen">Home screen</string>
    <string name="home_screen_widget">Home Screen Widget</string>
    <string name="hours">hours</string>
    <string name="how_to_add">How to add them?</string>
    <string name="how_to_enable_location">How to enable location</string>
    <string name="id_label">ID:</string>
    <string name="image_not_available">Image not available</string>
    <string name="image_processing_failed">Image processing failed</string>
    <string name="improvement_break_routine">Break out of the routine</string>
    <string name="improvement_create_strong_moment">Share something meaningful together</string>
    <string name="improvement_revive_connection">Revive our connection</string>
    <string name="improvement_say_unsaid">Open up like never before</string>
    <string name="invite_partner">Invite your partner</string>
    <string name="invite_partner_description">Enjoy the complete app experience together!</string>
    <string name="irreversible_action">This action is irreversible. The memory will be permanently deleted.</string>
    <string name="journal">Journal</string>
    <string name="journal_description">Start saving your favorite moments here and feel even closer together. \n\nYour partner will be able to see everything you add.</string>
    <string name="keep_going_unlock_all">Keep going and unlock all other questions and categories.</string>
    <string name="km">km</string>
    <string name="leave_review">Leave us a review</string>
    <string name="lets_go">Let\'s go!</string>
    <string name="limit_reached">Limit reached</string>
    <string name="listening_most_of_time">Yes, most of the time</string>
    <string name="listening_question">When a disagreement arises in your relationship, do you feel heard and understood?</string>
    <string name="listening_rarely">Rarely</string>
    <string name="listening_sometimes">Sometimes</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="loading_caps">LOADING...</string>
    <string name="loading_challenge">Loading your challenge...</string>
    <string name="loading_daily_question">Loading today\'s question...</string>
    <string name="loading_error">Loading error</string>
    <string name="loading_experience">Personalizing your experience...</string>
    <string name="loading_photos">Loading...</string>
    <string name="loading_preferences">Analyzing your preferences...</string>
    <string name="loading_profile">Preparing your profile...</string>
    <string name="loading_simple">Loading...</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="location_access_permission">Location access permission</string>
    <string name="location_permission">Location</string>
    <string name="location_permission_rationale">Love2Love uses your location to calculate the distance between you and your partner, and to allow you to add places to your shared memories.</string>
    <string name="location_place">Place</string>
    <string name="location_services_needed">Location services are needed for the app to calculate the distance between you and your partner.</string>
    <string name="location_status">Location</string>
    <string name="lock_screen">Lock screen</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_description">Tap your lock screen to start editing.</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_widget">Lock Screen Widget</string>
    <string name="locked_content">Premium Content</string>
    <string name="locked_icon">ðŸ”’</string>
    <string name="locked_widget">ðŸ”’</string>
    <string name="love_map_description">Find your memories on a unique map, and relive the moments that marked your love.</string>
    <string name="love_map_feature">âœ“ Create your love map</string>
    <string name="love_stronger_description">Unlock over 1,800 questions specially designed to bring you closer, discover facets of your partner you don\'t know yet, and above all establish healthy and sincere communication between you two.</string>
    <string name="love_stronger_feature">âœ“ To love each other even stronger</string>
    <string name="lph_1">Do you have a fantasy you haven\'t dared to bring up with me yet?</string>
    <string name="lph_10">What outfit makes you want me most?</string>
    <string name="lph_100">What are your three main pleasures?</string>
    <string name="lph_101">What do you like to do after making love?</string>
    <string name="lph_102">Are there fun ways that would please you during our intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_103">Would you like to incorporate food like whipped cream, chocolate sauce or edible underwear into our lovemaking?</string>
    <string name="lph_104">Do you like dirty talk?</string>
    <string name="lph_105">Do you want me to send you more sensual messages?</string>
    <string name="lph_106">Do you like listening to music during intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_107">What did you find most attractive about me during our first meeting?</string>
    <string name="lph_108">What happened in your last naughty dream?</string>
    <string name="lph_109">What musical atmosphere makes you want a carnal moment with me?</string>
    <string name="lph_11">What is your favorite place to receive a kiss?</string>
    <string name="lph_110">Do you think sensual chemistry can be worked on?</string>
    <string name="lph_111">Do you sometimes feel embarrassed during our intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_112">What importance do you place on sexual relations in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="lph_113">How do you think our sex life will evolve in the future?</string>
    <string name="lph_114">What do you consider as infidelity?</string>
    <string name="lph_115">How do you think your love language influences your preferences in bed?</string>
    <string name="lph_116">How can I help you feel more desired?</string>
    <string name="lph_117">Do you think we talk about our sexuality openly and honestly?</string>
    <string name="lph_118">How could we improve our sex life?</string>
    <string name="lph_119">What are the non-negotiable limits in our sex life?</string>
    <string name="lph_12">Do you feel fully satisfied sexually speaking with me?</string>
    <string name="lph_120">What is a word or phrase that instantly awakens your desire?</string>
    <string name="lph_121">What is your favorite moment in an intimate exchange: the beginning, the heart or the after?</string>
    <string name="lph_122">What type of foreplay do you appreciate most?</string>
    <string name="lph_123">Do you have sexual limits or taboos you\'d like to talk about?</string>
    <string name="lph_124">Do you like hearing my breathing during our intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_125">Do you think we should massage each other more often?</string>
    <string name="lph_126">What is the part of your body where you\'d like me to massage you more often?</string>
    <string name="lph_127">What is your best way to show your desire without words?</string>
    <string name="lph_128">What do you think about reading or listening to erotic stories together?</string>
    <string name="lph_129">What is the most daring thing you want to try at least once in your life?</string>
    <string name="lph_13">What is the best frequency for having sex according to you?</string>
    <string name="lph_130">How would you like me to seduce you?</string>
    <string name="lph_131">Are there past experiences you\'d like to draw inspiration from for our future adventures?</string>
    <string name="lph_132">What is the most sensual compliment I could give you?</string>
    <string name="lph_133">Are there regrets or missed moments you\'d like to discuss?</string>
    <string name="lph_134">What would you like me to do more often to surprise you?</string>
    <string name="lph_135">Is there something you\'ve never dared to suggest to me out of modesty?</string>
    <string name="lph_136">How has communication about desires and limits evolved for you over the years?</string>
    <string name="lph_137">Are there past experiences you find difficult to share or overcome?</string>
    <string name="lph_138">How did you discover what pleases you most from an erotic point of view?</string>
    <string name="lph_139">How do trust and security in a relationship affect your openness to intimate experiences?</string>
    <string name="lph_14">Do you have a song that makes you want me?</string>
    <string name="lph_140">What makes a sensual moment unforgettable according to you?</string>
    <string name="lph_141">How do you prefer us to initiate making love?</string>
    <string name="lph_142">Is there a rhythm, slowness or intensity you prefer?</string>
    <string name="lph_143">At what exact time of day do you feel most drawn to making love?</string>
    <string name="lph_144">Is there a routine or ritual that puts you in the ideal mindset for love?</string>
    <string name="lph_145">What type of music or sound ambiance puts you in the mood to make love?</string>
    <string name="lph_146">If you had to write me a letter of desire, what would you slip into it?</string>
    <string name="lph_147">What non-sexual activities make you feel closest to me?</string>
    <string name="lph_148">How do you like us to communicate when we make love?</string>
    <string name="lph_149">What type of touch do you find most comforting or exciting?</string>
    <string name="lph_15">What part of your body should I explore more often according to you?</string>
    <string name="lph_150">Are there foods or flavors that put you in a romantic or sensual mood?</string>
    <string name="lph_151">What is your favorite type of kiss and why?</string>
    <string name="lph_152">How would you define the perfect balance between tenderness and passion?</string>
    <string name="lph_153">What importance do you place on foreplay? Are there specific aspects you prefer?</string>
    <string name="lph_154">What is your most sensitive zone?</string>
    <string name="lph_155">If I had to make you vibrate just with words, what would you want to hear?</string>
    <string name="lph_156">During the moment we make love, what makes you want to slow down time?</string>
    <string name="lph_157">What is your favorite way to receive a kiss?</string>
    <string name="lph_158">How do you like us to end when we make love?</string>
    <string name="lph_159">What are the little attentions or gestures that make you feel desired?</string>
    <string name="lph_16">What type of massage turns you on, even if it doesn\'t seem like it?</string>
    <string name="lph_160">What is the most romantic experience you\'d like to live together?</string>
    <string name="lph_161">How does distance or time spent apart affect your desire for me?</string>
    <string name="lph_162">If you had to imagine our next intimate moment, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="lph_163">What are the most sensual memories we\'ve shared that are dear to your heart?</string>
    <string name="lph_164">What is the most unexpected moment when your desire for me awakened quickly?</string>
    <string name="lph_165">Are there words or phrases that make you uncomfortable during intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_166">Are there aspects of your sexuality or desires you find difficult to express?</string>
    <string name="lph_167">How can we approach taboo or sensitive subjects constructively?</string>
    <string name="lph_168">Are there past experiences that contributed to these limits or taboos?</string>
    <string name="lph_169">How do you feel about discussing our past sexual experiences?</string>
    <string name="lph_17">On a scale of 1 to 10, how much do you want me when I turn you on?</string>
    <string name="lph_170">Are there fantasies you hesitate to explore for ethical or moral reasons?</string>
    <string name="lph_171">How can we ensure our sexual experiences remain safe and consensual?</string>
    <string name="lph_172">What is your point of view on monogamy and exclusivity in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="lph_173">Are there discussions about sexuality you find particularly difficult or uncomfortable?</string>
    <string name="lph_174">Are there aspects of our intimacy you\'d like to deepen or modify to feel more comfortable?</string>
    <string name="lph_175">How do trust and security in our relationship impact your willingness to explore new sexual experiences?</string>
    <string name="lph_176">Are there aspects of our sexual relationship that need more dialogue or understanding?</string>
    <string name="lph_177">Is there a movement you find incredibly sensual when I do it?</string>
    <string name="lph_178">How have society and culture influenced your perceptions of sexual limits and taboos?</string>
    <string name="lph_179">Would you like me to take more initiative in our lovemaking?</string>
    <string name="lph_18">What is your favorite erotic or sensual memory with me?</string>
    <string name="lph_180">Would you like to test a seduction scenario, as if we had just met?</string>
    <string name="lph_181">Do you feel comfortable telling me when you don\'t want to do it?</string>
    <string name="lph_182">Do you think our communication about our desires is sufficient?</string>
    <string name="lph_183">Do you think we should reserve \'ritual\' moments to talk about our desires?</string>
    <string name="lph_184">Are you sometimes afraid of disappointing me sexually?</string>
    <string name="lph_185">Do you feel heard when you express your desires?</string>
    <string name="lph_186">Have you ever regretted not telling me about a particular desire?</string>
    <string name="lph_187">Do you feel free to tell me what you don\'t like during the act?</string>
    <string name="lph_188">Would you like us to challenge each other with erotic challenges to complete over a week?</string>
    <string name="lph_189">Have you ever wanted to try food during our lovemaking (chocolate, whipped cream...)?</string>
    <string name="lph_19">What is the simplest thing I can do that makes you want me, even just a little?</string>
    <string name="lph_190">Would you like us to explore \'slow kissing\' (very slow kisses) more?</string>
    <string name="lph_191">Have you ever been ashamed of a fantasy or desire?</string>
    <string name="lph_192">What is your favorite way to let me know you want me, without saying a word?</string>
    <string name="lph_193">Do you feel like our society judges certain desires too easily?</string>
    <string name="lph_194">Do you believe our sex life influences our daily happiness?</string>
    <string name="lph_195">Have you ever imagined what our sexuality would become in 10 years?</string>
    <string name="lph_196">What erotic discovery with me has marked you positively?</string>
    <string name="lph_197">Do you feel capable of suggesting initiatives more often to spice up our relationship?</string>
    <string name="lph_198">What do you appreciate most just after a sensual moment?</string>
    <string name="lph_199">Do you think discussion is important after an erotic moment?</string>
    <string name="lph_2">What is something I say that instantly turns you on?</string>
    <string name="lph_20">Do you have a place where you\'d dream of us being alone together?</string>
    <string name="lph_200">What would you like me to understand better about your desire?</string>
    <string name="lph_201">Do you agree that good communication is the key to fulfilled intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_202">What foreplay do you hate?</string>
    <string name="lph_203">What mundane moment has already made you want to touch me?</string>
    <string name="lph_204">Is there a specific emotion that always precedes your desire for me?</string>
    <string name="lph_205">Do you talk about our sex life with your friends?</string>
    <string name="lph_206">If we had to write a sensual scene together, what would be the setting?</string>
    <string name="lph_207">Do you find my body attractive?</string>
    <string name="lph_208">How can we revive sexual attraction between us?</string>
    <string name="lph_209">If sex was out of the question, would you stay with me?</string>
    <string name="lph_21">What caress soothes you but turns you on at the same time?</string>
    <string name="lph_210">What is the definition of eroticism for you?</string>
    <string name="lph_211">Do you think we don\'t let ourselves go enough under the sheets?</string>
    <string name="lph_212">What makes a kiss unforgettable according to you?</string>
    <string name="lph_213">What is the best way to reconnect when we\'ve missed each other?</string>
    <string name="lph_214">What gesture or attitude from me has already driven you crazy with desire?</string>
    <string name="lph_215">Is there a simple thing I do that immediately puts you in the mood?</string>
    <string name="lph_216">Do you prefer soft or firm caresses?</string>
    <string name="lph_217">How would you like me to give you confidence in your body again?</string>
    <string name="lph_218">What moment we spent together gives you butterflies?</string>
    <string name="lph_219">What is your biggest desire right now?</string>
    <string name="lph_22">Do you think we share enough moments making love together?</string>
    <string name="lph_220">Do you have a favorite cuisine for our romantic dinners?</string>
    <string name="lph_221">If you could fall asleep in only one position with me, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="lph_222">What do you find beautiful in our gestures when we love each other?</string>
    <string name="lph_223">What is something you\'ve never dared to say about what you like to receive?</string>
    <string name="lph_224">What perfume do you recommend I wear?</string>
    <string name="lph_225">If your body could speak, what would it ask of me?</string>
    <string name="lph_226">What moment have you perceived as the purest expression of our mutual desire?</string>
    <string name="lph_227">What would you like to do on a morning when we\'re both together, without constraints?</string>
    <string name="lph_228">What is your favorite naughty couple activity?</string>
    <string name="lph_229">Describe the perfect wake-up.</string>
    <string name="lph_23">Do you think sexual relations are a good way to reconcile?</string>
    <string name="lph_230">What makes a moment unforgettable for you, even without words?</string>
    <string name="lph_231">Was there a time when you felt more than pleasure: a real connection?</string>
    <string name="lph_232">Would it be harder to stop sex for 1 year or not see each other for 3 months?</string>
    <string name="lph_233">What do you think of the movie 50 Shades of Grey?</string>
    <string name="lph_234">Where would you like to spend your honeymoon?</string>
    <string name="lph_235">If you could, where would you kiss me on my body?</string>
    <string name="lph_236">What is your favorite form of touch: hands, skin, breath...?</string>
    <string name="lph_237">Rather pajamas or sexy outfit?</string>
    <string name="lph_238">What physical detail between us is engraved in your sensory memory?</string>
    <string name="lph_239">What do you think about kisses in public?</string>
    <string name="lph_24">What is the last time you really wanted me?</string>
    <string name="lph_240">If I could teleport to your door right now, how would you welcome me?</string>
    <string name="lph_241">What is the naughtiest emoji according to you?</string>
    <string name="lph_242">According to you, what is the most aphrodisiac food?</string>
    <string name="lph_243">What do you prefer about your body?</string>
    <string name="lph_244">Do you prefer tender caresses or slightly wilder ones?</string>
    <string name="lph_245">What carnal moment made you feel loved beyond the physical?</string>
    <string name="lph_246">Do you find me tender enough with you?</string>
    <string name="lph_247">How could I make you feel that I\'m there, even without touching you?</string>
    <string name="lph_248">What physical act between us has already soothed and excited you at the same time?</string>
    <string name="lph_249">On a scale of 1 to 10, how important is sexuality for you in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="lph_25">What is something I do that feels good to you without me knowing it?</string>
    <string name="lph_250">What was, according to you, the time when our foreplay really turned you on? and why?</string>
    <string name="lph_251">Do you prefer foreplay to be the main event or just a prelude?</string>
    <string name="lph_252">Do you prefer to show affection in public or in private?</string>
    <string name="lph_253">Do you prefer me to be very talkative or stay silent in bed?</string>
    <string name="lph_254">If our next embrace was the last, what would you want us to do?</string>
    <string name="lph_255">After all these questions, do you think we\'ll be able to please each other even more?</string>
    <string name="lph_256">What did you retain from all my answers?</string>
    <string name="lph_26">What is the moment when you felt the most desire for me?</string>
    <string name="lph_27">What romantic or sensual scene from a movie made you want to experience it?</string>
    <string name="lph_28">What is the time of day when you want it most?</string>
    <string name="lph_29">Which of my underwear do you like the most?</string>
    <string name="lph_3">What is the part of my body you love most?</string>
    <string name="lph_30">What is your definition of perfect intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_31">What would you like me to whisper to you during our intimate moments?</string>
    <string name="lph_32">If I had to surprise you gently, how should I go about it?</string>
    <string name="lph_33">What naughty thought comes to you when you think about me?</string>
    <string name="lph_34">What is the second part of my body you love most?</string>
    <string name="lph_35">Is there a perfume or scent that awakens your desire for me?</string>
    <string name="lph_36">What is your favorite way to show me you want me?</string>
    <string name="lph_37">Do you remember the very first time you wanted me? Describe it to me.</string>
    <string name="lph_38">What is the unexpected moment when you felt desire for me?</string>
    <string name="lph_39">Have you ever had a strong desire for me in the middle of the day, for no apparent reason?</string>
    <string name="lph_4">Have you ever had an erotic dream about me? If so, describe it to me.</string>
    <string name="lph_40">Do you think abstinence could be a way to stoke even more desire for each other?</string>
    <string name="lph_41">What do I do without realizing it that attracts you physically?</string>
    <string name="lph_42">Do you think I do well at turning you on?</string>
    <string name="lph_43">According to you, how could we add even more spice and desire during our intimacy?</string>
    <string name="lph_44">Have I ever turned you on just with my look?</string>
    <string name="lph_45">Is there something I could do to make you want me even more?</string>
    <string name="lph_46">Is there a moment we spent together that you find particularly exciting just thinking about it?</string>
    <string name="lph_47">What would you like me to do more slowly to prolong the pleasure?</string>
    <string name="lph_48">What emotion often precedes your desire for me?</string>
    <string name="lph_49">Be honest, do you feel fully satisfied sexually with me?</string>
    <string name="lph_5">Is there an erotic scenario you\'d like us to do together?</string>
    <string name="lph_50">Do you have an idea for a romantic and sensual surprise you\'d like to organize?</string>
    <string name="lph_51">If you could invent an evening dedicated to our sensual pleasure, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="lph_52">Would you like me to tell you certain things more often to turn you on even more?</string>
    <string name="lph_53">If you had to give me the perfect plan to turn you on, what would you tell me?</string>
    <string name="lph_54">Do you prefer I turn you on with words or actions?</string>
    <string name="lph_55">What simple gesture has already made your desire rise very quickly?</string>
    <string name="lph_56">Are you more of a morning or evening person?</string>
    <string name="lph_57">Do you like having control or letting me guide you?</string>
    <string name="lph_58">Do you feel fully desired by me or would you like me to show you even more my desire for you?</string>
    <string name="lph_59">What is the most romantic thing that excites you more than one might think?</string>
    <string name="lph_6">What is a moment when I turned you on without even realizing it?</string>
    <string name="lph_60">What are some things you\'d like me to say to you during our intimate moments?</string>
    <string name="lph_61">What is your way of telling me you want me without really saying it?</string>
    <string name="lph_62">When you think about us making love, what is the detail that often comes back?</string>
    <string name="lph_63">Ideally, how many times should we do it per week?</string>
    <string name="lph_64">According to you, what is the ideal duration for foreplay?</string>
    <string name="lph_65">What is your secret pleasure you don\'t dare confess to me?</string>
    <string name="lph_66">What is a gesture or word from me that always makes you feel desired?</string>
    <string name="lph_67">Is there a moment when you surprised yourself desiring something new with me?</string>
    <string name="lph_68">What turns you on the fastest?</string>
    <string name="lph_69">Where do you like me to touch you most?</string>
    <string name="lph_7">Do you like when I moan?</string>
    <string name="lph_70">What is the most unexpected place where you\'ve ever wanted me?</string>
    <string name="lph_71">What is something you\'ve always wanted to do but haven\'t told me yet for fear I wouldn\'t like it?</string>
    <string name="lph_72">What color of my underwear makes you want me most?</string>
    <string name="lph_73">Where would you like me to kiss you more?</string>
    <string name="lph_74">If I had to make you want me without speaking, what would you expect from me?</string>
    <string name="lph_75">Would you like me to send you more sensual photos of myself?</string>
    <string name="lph_76">Is there a place where you\'d like me to turn you on?</string>
    <string name="lph_77">What is your most receptive zone during our moments of tenderness?</string>
    <string name="lph_78">If we created together a perfect moment to reconnect physically, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="lph_79">When do you feel most irresistible in my eyes?</string>
    <string name="lph_8">Have you ever imagined an erotic moment in an unlikely place with me?</string>
    <string name="lph_80">Has my presence ever made you want me without me saying or doing anything special?</string>
    <string name="lph_81">What is a look or touch from me that you find irresistible?</string>
    <string name="lph_82">What would you like me to wear the next time we see each other?</string>
    <string name="lph_83">Do you prefer giving or receiving?</string>
    <string name="lph_84">Are you more cuddly or kissy?</string>
    <string name="lph_85">What is something I do that turns you on and you hope I never stop doing?</string>
    <string name="lph_86">What would you like me to do to you during our next lovemaking?</string>
    <string name="lph_87">If I had one minute to turn you on, what should I do?</string>
    <string name="lph_88">What about me awakens your playful side?</string>
    <string name="lph_89">Do you think I\'m getting better and better at turning you on?</string>
    <string name="lph_9">What makes you want me most when you think about me right now?</string>
    <string name="lph_90">What is your favorite way to initiate an intimate moment?</string>
    <string name="lph_91">What could we do to increase our mutual desire even more?</string>
    <string name="lph_92">What is your most beautiful erotic surprise in our relationship so far?</string>
    <string name="lph_93">If I asked you to guide me, where would you take me on your body?</string>
    <string name="lph_94">What makes you want to keep me close to you all night?</string>
    <string name="lph_95">If you had to give me advice to turn you on even more, what would you tell me?</string>
    <string name="lph_96">What do I do that you like to watch?</string>
    <string name="lph_97">Do you prefer to describe what you\'d like to try in bed verbally in real life or by text?</string>
    <string name="lph_98">Do you prefer to plan when we do it or make it more spontaneous?</string>
    <string name="lph_99">What is the most subtle way I can show you my desire for you?</string>
    <string name="max_64_questions">64 questions max (free category)</string>
    <string name="me_10">Is there a vulnerability you\'d like to be able to share fearlessly with me?</string>
    <string name="me_100">What\'s the thing you never want to lose in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_101">What makes you feel you can be completely yourself with me?</string>
    <string name="me_102">If our relationship had a symbol, what would it be and why?</string>
    <string name="me_103">How could I better respect your pace in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_104">What would you like me to understand more about your way of loving?</string>
    <string name="me_105">What question would you like me to ask you more often?</string>
    <string name="me_106">How can you help me express myself better with you?</string>
    <string name="me_107">What future difficulty would you like us to be ready to face together?</string>
    <string name="me_108">How can you feel freer in our couple without detaching yourself?</string>
    <string name="me_109">Is there something we could do to re-enchant our daily life?</string>
    <string name="me_11">What helps you feel heard in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_110">When do you feel our love is strongest?</string>
    <string name="me_111">If I gave you more space, what would you do with it?</string>
    <string name="me_112">What dream seems more possible since we\'ve been together?</string>
    <string name="me_113">What do you feel when we go through a prolonged silence between us?</string>
    <string name="me_114">What would you like us to do together to reconnect after a difficult moment?</string>
    <string name="me_115">When did you want to thank me but didn\'t do it?</string>
    <string name="me_116">What part of you has changed since we\'ve been together?</string>
    <string name="me_117">If I listened to you even better, what would I understand about you?</string>
    <string name="me_118">What memory of us helps you keep confidence in our future?</string>
    <string name="me_119">When did you feel most desired by me?</string>
    <string name="me_12">Is there a habit we could create together?</string>
    <string name="me_120">What would be our perfect song to reconcile after a conflict?</string>
    <string name="me_121">Is there a moment when you felt excluded from my priorities?</string>
    <string name="me_122">What\'s the most beautiful thing you\'d like to hear from me?</string>
    <string name="me_123">How would you like me to react when you\'re angry?</string>
    <string name="me_124">What moment together made you say: \'This is the right person\'?</string>
    <string name="me_125">Is there a part of you that you haven\'t revealed to me yet?</string>
    <string name="me_126">What\'s the most important thing you\'d like me to remember about you?</string>
    <string name="me_127">How would you like us to celebrate our small victories together?</string>
    <string name="me_128">What makes you smile when you think of us?</string>
    <string name="me_129">What common habit would you like us to develop?</string>
    <string name="me_13">When did you feel that I understood you without you having to say a word?</string>
    <string name="me_130">Is there something you\'d want us to stop doing together?</string>
    <string name="me_131">What moment in our relationship made you grow the most?</string>
    <string name="me_132">How can you help me be more patient with you?</string>
    <string name="me_133">What\'s the thing you appreciate most about my way of loving you?</string>
    <string name="me_134">If we had to make a promise for the next 10 years, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="me_135">What makes you want to build a future with me?</string>
    <string name="me_136">What challenge would you like us to take on together this year?</string>
    <string name="me_137">How would you like us to handle our disagreements in the future?</string>
    <string name="me_138">What\'s the thing you never want me to forget about you?</string>
    <string name="me_139">What moment between us deserves to be celebrated more?</string>
    <string name="me_14">What\'s the most beautiful thing you\'ve learned through our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_140">How could I better support you in your difficult moments?</string>
    <string name="me_141">What part of our story would you like to rewrite?</string>
    <string name="me_142">What makes you feel most connected to me?</string>
    <string name="me_143">What aspect of our relationship makes you most proud?</string>
    <string name="me_144">How would you like us to evolve together in the coming years?</string>
    <string name="me_145">What\'s the thing you\'d like us to do more spontaneously?</string>
    <string name="me_146">What memory of us would you like to create in the coming months?</string>
    <string name="me_147">How can I better honor your needs in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_148">What truth about our couple would you like us to accept together?</string>
    <string name="me_149">What makes you feel that our love is unique?</string>
    <string name="me_15">Is there a time when you wished I had been more present?</string>
    <string name="me_150">What dream would you like us to achieve together before the end of the year?</string>
    <string name="me_151">How would you like us to rediscover each other?</string>
    <string name="me_152">What habit could I change to make you happier?</string>
    <string name="me_153">What gives you confidence in our ability to overcome obstacles?</string>
    <string name="me_154">What moment of tenderness between us marked you the most?</string>
    <string name="me_155">How would you like us to support each other in our projects?</string>
    <string name="me_156">What\'s the thing you\'d like us to share more?</string>
    <string name="me_157">What aspect of our intimacy would you like to deepen?</string>
    <string name="me_158">How can I better show you that I care about you?</string>
    <string name="me_159">What important lesson has our relationship taught you?</string>
    <string name="me_16">How could I better support your dreams or projects?</string>
    <string name="me_160">What makes you feel that I\'m the right person for you?</string>
    <string name="me_161">How would you like us to cultivate our daily complicity?</string>
    <string name="me_162">What promise would you like us to renew regularly?</string>
    <string name="me_163">What makes you say that our love is worth all the effort?</string>
    <string name="me_164">What positive change would you like to bring to our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_165">How can I better respect your pace and needs?</string>
    <string name="me_166">What tradition would you like us to create together?</string>
    <string name="me_167">What makes you feel truly heard by me?</string>
    <string name="me_168">What moment of our daily life would you like to make more special?</string>
    <string name="me_169">How would you like us to remember why we love each other?</string>
    <string name="me_17">What simple gesture has the most value for you in our daily life?</string>
    <string name="me_170">What\'s the thing you\'d like us to improve in our communication?</string>
    <string name="me_171">What makes you feel that we form a real team?</string>
    <string name="me_172">What aspect of our relationship would you like to preserve at all costs?</string>
    <string name="me_173">How can I better make you feel that you\'re my priority?</string>
    <string name="me_174">What surprise would you like to give me to bring us closer?</string>
    <string name="me_175">What makes you want to continue growing with me?</string>
    <string name="me_176">What difficult moment made us more united?</string>
    <string name="me_177">How would you like us to celebrate our love daily?</string>
    <string name="me_178">What part of yourself would you still like me to discover?</string>
    <string name="me_179">What makes you feel that our relationship is precious?</string>
    <string name="me_18">Have you ever been afraid of losing me? Why?</string>
    <string name="me_180">What common goal would you like us to set?</string>
    <string name="me_181">How can I better show you my gratitude for your love?</string>
    <string name="me_182">What habit would you like us to abandon to get closer?</string>
    <string name="me_183">What makes you feel that I truly understand you?</string>
    <string name="me_184">What moment of joy would you like us to relive together?</string>
    <string name="me_185">How would you like us to support each other in our moments of doubt?</string>
    <string name="me_186">What quality in me helps you feel loved?</string>
    <string name="me_187">What makes you believe in our future together?</string>
    <string name="me_188">What simple gesture could improve our daily life?</string>
    <string name="me_189">How would you like us to preserve the magic of our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_19">What do you feel when we argue?</string>
    <string name="me_190">What\'s the thing you\'d like us to experiment with together?</string>
    <string name="me_191">What makes you feel that our love is authentic?</string>
    <string name="me_192">What moment of silence between us felt the strongest?</string>
    <string name="me_193">How can I better accompany you in your personal challenges?</string>
    <string name="me_194">What part of our story would you like us to tell our children?</string>
    <string name="me_195">What makes you feel that we\'re growing together?</string>
    <string name="me_196">What crazy dream would you like us to pursue together?</string>
    <string name="me_197">How would you like us to regain momentum when we stagnate?</string>
    <string name="me_198">What truth about me would you like me to accept better?</string>
    <string name="me_199">What makes you feel that our relationship is balanced?</string>
    <string name="me_2">What would you like us to change to better listen to each other?</string>
    <string name="me_20">What quality in me helps you feel secure?</string>
    <string name="me_200">What moment of our relationship would you like us to immortalize?</string>
    <string name="me_201">How would you like us to remember our beginnings together?</string>
    <string name="me_202">What lesson of love would you like us to transmit to others?</string>
    <string name="me_203">What makes you feel that I\'m your good complement?</string>
    <string name="me_204">What relationship challenge would you like us to overcome together?</string>
    <string name="me_205">How can I better honor the trust you place in me?</string>
    <string name="me_206">What habit of love would you like us to cultivate?</string>
    <string name="me_207">What makes you feel that our bond is indestructible?</string>
    <string name="me_208">What moment of our relationship made you evolve the most?</string>
    <string name="me_209">How would you like us to prepare for future challenges?</string>
    <string name="me_21">Is there something you\'ve never dared to ask me?</string>
    <string name="me_210">What part of our love would you like us to explore more?</string>
    <string name="me_211">What makes you feel that we\'re made for each other?</string>
    <string name="me_212">What ritual would you like us to establish to reconnect?</string>
    <string name="me_213">How can I better show you that your happiness matters to me?</string>
    <string name="me_214">What promise would you like us to make for the future?</string>
    <string name="me_215">What makes you feel that our love deserves all efforts?</string>
    <string name="me_216">What aspect of our relationship would you like us to celebrate more often?</string>
    <string name="me_217">How would you like us to remember this period of our life?</string>
    <string name="me_218">What quality would you like us to develop together?</string>
    <string name="me_219">What makes you feel that I\'m your refuge?</string>
    <string name="me_22">How do you react when you feel misunderstood by me?</string>
    <string name="me_220">What moment of complicity would you like us to recreate?</string>
    <string name="me_221">How can I better make you feel that you\'re irreplaceable?</string>
    <string name="me_222">What adventure would you like us to live together?</string>
    <string name="me_223">What makes you feel that our story is extraordinary?</string>
    <string name="me_224">What change in our routine could bring us closer?</string>
    <string name="me_225">How would you like us to tell each other our love again?</string>
    <string name="me_226">What part of our future excites you most?</string>
    <string name="me_227">What makes you feel that we\'re evolving in the right direction?</string>
    <string name="me_228">What moment of our relationship would you like us to extend?</string>
    <string name="me_229">How can I better show you that I choose to love you every day?</string>
    <string name="me_23">What would you like us to do more often together?</string>
    <string name="me_230">What lesson from our relationship would you like us never to forget?</string>
    <string name="me_231">What makes you feel that our love is mature?</string>
    <string name="me_232">What shared dream would you like us to realize first?</string>
    <string name="me_233">How would you like us to support each other in our individual projects?</string>
    <string name="me_234">What couple tradition would you like us to invent?</string>
    <string name="me_235">What makes you feel that I truly see you?</string>
    <string name="me_236">What moment of our relationship gave you the most hope?</string>
    <string name="me_237">How would you like us to handle our differences?</string>
    <string name="me_238">What part of our emotional intimacy would you like to deepen?</string>
    <string name="me_239">What makes you feel that we\'re creating something beautiful together?</string>
    <string name="me_24">What touches you most when I talk about you to others?</string>
    <string name="me_240">What aspect of our love would you like us to protect the most?</string>
    <string name="me_241">How can I better make you feel that you\'re my absolute priority?</string>
    <string name="me_242">What surprise would you like us to give each other?</string>
    <string name="me_243">What makes you feel that our relationship is a gift?</string>
    <string name="me_244">What moment of our daily life would you like to turn into a ritual?</string>
    <string name="me_245">How would you like us to remember our common values?</string>
    <string name="me_246">What part of our love story are you most proud of?</string>
    <string name="me_247">What makes you feel that we\'re building something lasting?</string>
    <string name="me_248">What challenge would you like us to transform into a growth opportunity?</string>
    <string name="me_249">How can I better show you that your fulfillment matters to me?</string>
    <string name="me_25">How do you know I love you, even when I don\'t say it?</string>
    <string name="me_250">What promise would you like us to renew each year?</string>
    <string name="me_251">What makes you feel that our love transcends difficulties?</string>
    <string name="me_252">What moment of our relationship would you like us to savor more?</string>
    <string name="me_253">How would you like us to cultivate our mutual gratitude?</string>
    <string name="me_254">What quality of our relationship would you like us to transmit around us?</string>
    <string name="me_255">What makes you feel that I\'m your ideal life partner?</string>
    <string name="me_256">What legacy of love would you like us to leave together?</string>
    <string name="me_26">Have you ever needed space without knowing how to tell me?</string>
    <string name="me_27">What habit could bring us even closer?</string>
    <string name="me_28">What helps you forgive in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_29">Do you sometimes feel like you\'re not enough in our couple?</string>
    <string name="me_3">When have you felt fully aligned with me in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_30">If we had to write a love letter together, what would you want it to say?</string>
    <string name="me_31">What shared experience has marked you the most?</string>
    <string name="me_32">What would you have liked me to do differently on an important day?</string>
    <string name="me_33">If our love were a season, which would it be and why?</string>
    <string name="me_34">Is there a difficult truth you\'d like us to address together?</string>
    <string name="me_35">What do I do without realizing it that touches you deeply?</string>
    <string name="me_36">What activity makes you feel most connected to me?</string>
    <string name="me_37">How would you like me to reassure you when you doubt?</string>
    <string name="me_38">If we had to take a break in our relationship, what would you want me to understand?</string>
    <string name="me_39">Is there an emotion you find difficult to express with me?</string>
    <string name="me_4">What simple gesture from me would brighten your day, even if I didn\'t realize it?</string>
    <string name="me_40">What makes you feel fully accepted by me?</string>
    <string name="me_41">What\'s your biggest insecurity in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_42">How can I better show you that I\'m really listening?</string>
    <string name="me_43">What would you like to build with me this year?</string>
    <string name="me_44">If we had to do couple\'s therapy, what would be the first topic to address?</string>
    <string name="me_45">Is there a memory you often relive in your head about us?</string>
    <string name="me_46">What part of our story would deserve to be told in a movie?</string>
    <string name="me_47">What difficult moment made us stronger?</string>
    <string name="me_48">When do you feel most loved by me?</string>
    <string name="me_49">What would you like us to do to maintain the magic between us?</string>
    <string name="me_5">What do you think makes our story different from all others?</string>
    <string name="me_50">How can you help me be a better version of myself?</string>
    <string name="me_51">What would you like us to try together, just for fun?</string>
    <string name="me_52">Is there a word or phrase you\'d like me to say to you more often?</string>
    <string name="me_53">What\'s the moment when you most felt our complicity?</string>
    <string name="me_54">Is there a place that symbolizes our love for you?</string>
    <string name="me_55">How could I love you better, without you having to ask?</string>
    <string name="me_56">What could strengthen our trust in each other?</string>
    <string name="me_57">If we wrote our own rules of love, what would you put first?</string>
    <string name="me_58">Is there something you do for me that I don\'t notice?</string>
    <string name="me_59">What small thing could improve our daily life together?</string>
    <string name="me_6">How do you imagine our complicity evolving in the years to come?</string>
    <string name="me_60">What moment between us made you want to commit even more?</string>
    <string name="me_61">When did you feel like we formed a real team?</string>
    <string name="me_62">What ordinary moment in our life makes you happy for no particular reason?</string>
    <string name="me_63">What makes you want to stay committed to our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_64">What difficulty strengthened your love for me?</string>
    <string name="me_65">If you could tell me a difficult truth without fear, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="me_66">Is there something I do that makes you feel less loved?</string>
    <string name="me_67">What\'s the most beautiful promise you\'d like us to make?</string>
    <string name="me_68">How do you imagine a perfect moment together?</string>
    <string name="me_69">What past wound could you help me heal?</string>
    <string name="me_7">If our relationship were a movie scene, which one would best represent it?</string>
    <string name="me_70">Is there something you\'d want us to forget so we could start over stronger?</string>
    <string name="me_71">What\'s the greatest lesson our couple has taught you?</string>
    <string name="me_72">When you\'re sad, what do you expect from me without telling me?</string>
    <string name="me_73">What truth about yourself would you like me to understand better?</string>
    <string name="me_74">What could we celebrate more often together?</string>
    <string name="me_75">How can you show me your love in a new way?</string>
    <string name="me_76">Is there a past argument you never really got over?</string>
    <string name="me_77">What makes our intimacy unique in your eyes?</string>
    <string name="me_78">If we had to reinvent our routine, what would you start with?</string>
    <string name="me_79">What word melts you when I say it to you?</string>
    <string name="me_8">What could I learn to do to love you even more truly?</string>
    <string name="me_80">What situation makes you feel sidelined in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="me_81">What habit reassures you about the strength of our bond?</string>
    <string name="me_82">How has our relationship influenced your vision of love?</string>
    <string name="me_83">What part of your vulnerability would you like me to protect more?</string>
    <string name="me_84">What simple thing has the power to ease tension between us?</string>
    <string name="me_85">What do I sometimes do without realizing it that hurts you?</string>
    <string name="me_86">What phrase should we say to each other more often?</string>
    <string name="me_87">How would you describe our love to someone who doesn\'t know us?</string>
    <string name="me_88">What change in our relationship has done you the most good?</string>
    <string name="me_89">Is there a place you\'d like us to go to rekindle our bond?</string>
    <string name="me_9">What type of attention would touch your heart more than any gift?</string>
    <string name="me_90">What do you observe in me when I say nothing but feel strongly?</string>
    <string name="me_91">What makes you most want to trust me?</string>
    <string name="me_92">How do you know I\'m always there for you, even in silence?</string>
    <string name="me_93">If we met today, what would you want to tell me from the beginning?</string>
    <string name="me_94">What moment of silence between us seemed stronger than words?</string>
    <string name="me_95">What is something you never say but would be important for me to hear?</string>
    <string name="me_96">How would you like us to support each other more when we doubt?</string>
    <string name="me_97">What\'s the last time you felt deeply understood by me?</string>
    <string name="me_98">If I had to surprise you tomorrow, what would really touch you?</string>
    <string name="me_99">When did you feel the need to get closer to me without daring to say it?</string>
    <string name="memories_appear_map">All your special moments will appear here on the map.</string>
    <string name="memory_box_description">Because every memory deserves its place. Gather your most beautiful moments in an intimate, unique and shared diary, just for you two.</string>
    <string name="memory_box_feature">âœ“ Build your memory box</string>
    <string name="memory_description_placeholder">Describe what made this moment special</string>
    <string name="memory_title_placeholder">Title of your memory</string>
    <string name="messaging_space_creation">Your chat is being created...</string>
    <string name="minutes">minutes</string>
    <string name="miss_you_so_much">I miss you so much</string>
    <string name="missing_auth_token">Missing authentication token</string>
    <string name="month_april">April</string>
    <string name="month_august">August</string>
    <string name="month_december">December</string>
    <string name="month_february">February</string>
    <string name="month_january">January</string>
    <string name="month_july">July</string>
    <string name="month_june">June</string>
    <string name="month_march">March</string>
    <string name="month_may">May</string>
    <string name="month_november">November</string>
    <string name="month_october">October</string>
    <string name="month_september">September</string>
    <string name="months_plural">months</string>
    <string name="months_singular">month</string>
    <string name="more_than_2000_questions">More than 1800 questions to ask your soulmate</string>
    <string name="more_than_days">More than</string>
    <string name="name_label">Name:</string>
    <string name="name_placeholder">Enter your first name</string>
    <string name="name_step_description">This information will help us personalize your experience.</string>
    <string name="name_step_title">What\'s your name?</string>
    <string name="network_error">Network error</string>
    <string name="new_cards">new cards</string>
    <string name="new_cards_added">New cards added!</string>
    <string name="new_features_unlocked">New features unlocked</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="no_accessible_photos">No accessible photos</string>
    <string name="no_accessible_photos_title">No accessible photos</string>
    <string name="no_challenge_available">No challenge available</string>
    <string name="no_commitment_cancel_anytime">No commitment, cancel anytime</string>
    <string name="no_events_today">No events today</string>
    <string name="no_image">No image</string>
    <string name="no_partner_connected">No partner connected</string>
    <string name="no_payment_required_now">Start your trial â€” no charge today</string>
    <string name="no_photos_accessible">No photos accessible</string>
    <string name="no_premium_access">No premium access</string>
    <string name="no_products_available">No products available. Check your connection.</string>
    <string name="no_purchase_to_restore">No purchase to restore</string>
    <string name="no_question_available">No question available</string>
    <string name="no_relationship_date">No relationship date set</string>
    <string name="not_authorized">You are not authorized to perform this action</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_description">Notifications de votre partenaire</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_name">Notifications</string>
    <string name="notification_daily_21h">Daily notification at 9 PM</string>
    <string name="notification_daily_reminder_body">Your daily question is ready! Connect with your partner.</string>
    <string name="notification_daily_reminder_title">ðŸ’• Daily Question</string>
    <string name="notification_new_message_title">ðŸ’¬ New message</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_denied_message">To receive daily questions, you need to enable notifications in your phone\'s settings.</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_denied_onboarding_message">You can enable notifications later in Settings to receive daily questions.</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_denied_title">Notifications disabled</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_explanation">We\'ll send you a notification every day at 9 PM with your daily question.</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_rationale">Love2Love sends you notifications when your partner messages you. You can disable these notifications at any time in settings.</string>
    <string name="notifications_activated">Notifications activated!</string>
    <string name="notifications_status_no_partner">Connect partner first</string>
    <string name="notifications_status_partner_needs">Partner needs notifications</string>
    <string name="notifications_status_ready">Ready!</string>
    <string name="notifications_status_unknown">Unknown status</string>
    <string name="notifications_status_user_needs">Enable notifications</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="on_count">of</string>
    <string name="on_me">me</string>
    <string name="onboarding_daily_question_benefits">Build deeper conversations, discover new things about each other, and create daily moments of connection.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_daily_question_subtitle">Receive daily questions to strengthen your relationship</string>
    <string name="onboarding_daily_question_title">Stay connected every day</string>
    <string name="onboarding_notification_explanation">You can always change this setting later in your phone\'s settings.</string>
    <string name="one_more_step">ONE MORE STEP!</string>
    <string name="open_settings">Open Settings</string>
    <string name="others">others...</string>
    <string name="our_distance">Our distance: </string>
    <string name="our_journal">Our journal</string>
    <string name="pack_completed">You have completed the pack.</string>
    <string name="pack_name">the pack...</string>
    <string name="partner">Partner</string>
    <string name="partner_connected">Partner connected:</string>
    <string name="partner_connected_status">ðŸ‘¥ Partner Connected</string>
    <string name="partner_location_request">Ask your partner to do the same to activate their location, otherwise the distance between you cannot be calculated.</string>
    <string name="partner_name">Partner:</string>
    <string name="partner_no_payment">Your partner won\'t have to pay anything</string>
    <string name="partner_not_connected">Partner not connected</string>
    <string name="partner_shared_by">Shared by: %@</string>
    <string name="partner_status">ðŸ‘¥ Partner Status</string>
    <string name="partner_status_title">ðŸ‘¥ Partner Status</string>
    <string name="partner_turn">Your partner\'s turn</string>
    <string name="paywall_challenges_subtitle">Every day, a new challenge to take on together. Simple but powerful gestures to nurture your complicity and break out of the routine. Your new challenges are waiting for you..</string>
    <string name="paywall_challenges_title">You\'ve reached the free challenges limit ðŸŽ¯</string>
    <string name="paywall_continue_button">Unlock Premium Access</string>
    <string name="paywall_page_title_challenges">Daily Challenges</string>
    <string name="paywall_page_title_questions">Daily Questions</string>
    <string name="paywall_questions_subtitle">Every day, a new question to strengthen your relationship, explore your emotions, and create deep memories with your partner. Your new questions are waiting for you..</string>
    <string name="paywall_questions_title">You\'ve reached the end of your 3 free questions ðŸ’Œ</string>
    <string name="per_user_per">/ user /</string>
    <string name="period_month">month</string>
    <string name="period_week">week</string>
    <string name="permission">Permission</string>
    <string name="permission_location">Location permission</string>
    <string name="permission_photos">Photo access permission</string>
    <string name="photo_access_add_photos">To add photos, please authorize access in Settings</string>
    <string name="photo_access_denied_message">Photo gallery access is required to add a profile photo. Please enable it in your device settings.</string>
    <string name="photo_access_description">Love2Love will only access photos you authorize</string>
    <string name="photo_access_permission">Photo access permission</string>
    <string name="photo_access_required">Photo access required</string>
    <string name="photo_permission_message">To use this feature, please authorize photo access in Settings.</string>
    <string name="photo_permission_rationale">Love2Love needs access to your photos to allow you to personalize your profile and add images to your shared memories in the couple\'s journal.</string>
    <string name="plan_monthly_free_trial">Monthly - 3 days free</string>
    <string name="plan_monthly_price">14,99â‚¬</string>
    <string name="plan_monthly_price_per_user">7,50â‚¬</string>
    <string name="plan_weekly">Weekly</string>
    <string name="plan_weekly_price">4,99â‚¬</string>
    <string name="plan_weekly_price_per_user">2,50â‚¬</string>
    <string name="plus_description">Tap the + button in the top left to add a new widget.</string>
    <string name="prad_10">What\'s the stupidest thing you\'ve done out of laziness?</string>
    <string name="prad_100">What\'s the stupidest moment you tried to do something mature but acted like a child?</string>
    <string name="prad_101">If you could replace all windows with anything else, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_102">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to get your pet to forgive you?</string>
    <string name="prad_103">If you had to create a new type of cooking class with completely crazy ingredients, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_104">What\'s the most embarrassing moment you tried to do something artistic but it was a disaster?</string>
    <string name="prad_105">If you could make a bathroom object have a completely different function, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_106">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done trying to stand out in a crowd?</string>
    <string name="prad_107">If you had to create a new type of theater where actors can only whisper, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="prad_108">What\'s the stupidest moment you tried to do something generous but it went wrong?</string>
    <string name="prad_109">If you could replace all faucets with any other way to get water, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_11">If you had to create a new dance based on a daily activity, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_110">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to make memories?</string>
    <string name="prad_111">If you had to create a new type of library with a completely crazy concept, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_112">What\'s the most embarrassing time you tried to do something spontaneous but planned everything?</string>
    <string name="prad_113">If your life had a blooper reel, what would be the highlight moment?</string>
    <string name="prad_114">If you could have a conversation with an object, which one would you choose and why?</string>
    <string name="prad_115">If you could create a new ice cream flavor inspired by your personality, what would it be called?</string>
    <string name="prad_116">If you could have a fictional character as a roommate, who would you choose and why?</string>
    <string name="prad_117">What animal sound can you make the best? I want to hear it!!</string>
    <string name="prad_118">What\'s the most ridiculous reason you burst out laughing in a serious situation?</string>
    <string name="prad_119">If you could talk to your past self, what hilarious advice would they give you?</string>
    <string name="prad_12">What\'s the most embarrassing time you were caught talking to yourself?</string>
    <string name="prad_120">What song lyric did you mishear and sing confidently?</string>
    <string name="prad_121">What\'s the funniest thing I\'ve done since we\'ve been together?</string>
    <string name="prad_122">If I were a pizza, what would be my topping? And why?</string>
    <string name="prad_123">If I were an object, which one would I be and why?</string>
    <string name="prad_124">Have you ever had a dream so funny that you woke up laughing?</string>
    <string name="prad_125">Tell me about the worst haircut you\'ve ever had.</string>
    <string name="prad_126">Tell me about a time you tried to be discreet and got caught.</string>
    <string name="prad_127">Tell me about a time you laughed when you absolutely weren\'t supposed to.</string>
    <string name="prad_13">If you could have any animal as a means of transportation, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_14">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve bought online at 3 AM?</string>
    <string name="prad_15">If you had to create a new sport using everyday objects, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="prad_16">What\'s the most creative lie you\'ve invented to avoid a social event?</string>
    <string name="prad_17">If you could replace your voice with anyone else\'s for a day, who would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_18">What\'s the strangest thing you\'ve done when you thought you were alone?</string>
    <string name="prad_19">If you had to create a new emoji, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="prad_2">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done to avoid an awkward conversation?</string>
    <string name="prad_20">What\'s the most absurd moment when you burst out laughing?</string>
    <string name="prad_21">If you could make one inanimate object able to talk, which one would you choose and why?</string>
    <string name="prad_22">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done to impress someone?</string>
    <string name="prad_23">If you had to create a completely absurd new TV game show, what would be the main rule?</string>
    <string name="prad_24">What\'s the most embarrassing moment you confused someone with someone else?</string>
    <string name="prad_25">If you could have any useless but impressive skill, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_26">What\'s the strangest thing you\'ve done out of habit without realizing it?</string>
    <string name="prad_27">If you had to create a completely useless new job, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_28">What\'s the most absurd moment you tried to pretend you knew something you didn\'t?</string>
    <string name="prad_29">If you could replace all elevators with any other means of transportation, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_3">If you had to create a perfume that smells like your personality, what would it smell like?</string>
    <string name="prad_30">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done when you were sick?</string>
    <string name="prad_31">If you had to create a completely absurd new family tradition, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_32">What\'s the most embarrassing time you mispronounced a word in front of a crowd?</string>
    <string name="prad_33">If you could make a sound follow someone you don\'t like everywhere, what sound would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_34">What\'s the stupidest thing you\'ve done trying to appear intelligent?</string>
    <string name="prad_35">If you had to create a new type of restaurant with a completely crazy concept, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_36">What\'s the most absurd moment you tried to lie to your parents?</string>
    <string name="prad_37">If you could replace all door handles with anything else, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_38">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done thinking no one was watching?</string>
    <string name="prad_39">If you had to create a new type of public transportation, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="prad_4">What\'s the most absurd lie you told as a child and truly believed?</string>
    <string name="prad_40">What\'s the most embarrassing time you were caught procrastinating?</string>
    <string name="prad_41">If you could make one everyday object huge, which one would you choose to create the most chaos?</string>
    <string name="prad_42">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done to avoid cleaning?</string>
    <string name="prad_43">If you had to create a new type of exercise based on a ridiculous activity, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_44">What\'s the stupidest moment you tried to do something you saw in a movie?</string>
    <string name="prad_45">If you could replace all traffic lights with anything else, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_46">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done while half asleep?</string>
    <string name="prad_47">If you had to create a completely absurd new contest, what would be the main challenge?</string>
    <string name="prad_48">What\'s the most embarrassing moment you tried to be cool but everything went wrong?</string>
    <string name="prad_49">If you could make one food have a completely different texture, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_5">If you could replace all car horns with any sound, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_50">What\'s the stupidest thing you\'ve done trying to save money?</string>
    <string name="prad_51">If you had to create a new type of store with a completely crazy concept, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_52">What\'s the most absurd moment you tried to fix something and broke everything?</string>
    <string name="prad_53">If you could replace all phones with any other object to communicate, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_54">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to impress your friends?</string>
    <string name="prad_55">If you had to create a new type of entertainment based on a boring activity, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_56">What\'s the most embarrassing moment you confused two people on the phone?</string>
    <string name="prad_57">If you could make a piece of clothing have a completely useless function, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_58">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done trying to get noticed?</string>
    <string name="prad_59">If you had to create a new type of board game with completely crazy rules, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_6">What\'s the strangest thing you\'ve found in your fridge that you don\'t remember putting there?</string>
    <string name="prad_60">What\'s the silliest time you tried to do something romantic but it backfired?</string>
    <string name="prad_61">If you could replace all mirrors with anything else, what would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_62">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to get revenge on someone?</string>
    <string name="prad_63">If you had to create a completely useless new course, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_64">What\'s the most embarrassing time you tried to pretend to like something you hated?</string>
    <string name="prad_65">If you could make a piece of furniture have a completely different function, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_66">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done trying to get forgiveness?</string>
    <string name="prad_67">If you had to create a new type of festival with a completely crazy theme, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_68">What\'s the stupidest moment you tried to do something creative but it was a disaster?</string>
    <string name="prad_69">If you could replace all chairs with any other type of seat, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_7">If you had to survive a week with only the objects currently in your pocket/bag, how would you manage?</string>
    <string name="prad_70">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to avoid someone?</string>
    <string name="prad_71">If you had to create a new type of therapy based on a ridiculous activity, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_72">What\'s the most embarrassing time you tried to make a joke that fell flat?</string>
    <string name="prad_73">If you could make a household appliance have a personality, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_74">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done trying to relax?</string>
    <string name="prad_75">If you had to create a new type of competition with completely crazy rules, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_76">What\'s the stupidest moment you tried to do something heroic but failed?</string>
    <string name="prad_77">If you could replace all stairs with any other way to go up, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_78">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to make friends?</string>
    <string name="prad_79">If you had to create a new type of music based on everyday sounds, what would it sound like?</string>
    <string name="prad_8">What\'s the weirdest dream you\'ve had that you still remember?</string>
    <string name="prad_80">What\'s the most embarrassing time you tried to dance and everyone stared at you?</string>
    <string name="prad_81">If you could make an office object have a completely different function, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_82">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done trying to educate yourself?</string>
    <string name="prad_83">If you had to create a new type of vacation with a completely crazy concept, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_84">What\'s the stupidest moment you tried to do something sophisticated but failed?</string>
    <string name="prad_85">If you could replace all doors with any other type of entrance, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_86">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to save time?</string>
    <string name="prad_87">If you had to create a completely useless new hobby, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="prad_88">What\'s the most embarrassing time you tried to pretend to understand something you didn\'t understand?</string>
    <string name="prad_89">If you could make a pet have a human skill, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_9">If you could make one food scream when eaten, which one would you choose to create the most chaos?</string>
    <string name="prad_90">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done trying to motivate yourself?</string>
    <string name="prad_91">If you had to create a new type of restaurant where everything is upside down, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="prad_92">What\'s the stupidest moment you tried to do something romantic for yourself?</string>
    <string name="prad_93">If you could replace all beds with any other type of sleeping arrangement, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_94">What\'s the most ridiculous thing you\'ve done trying to get your crush to notice you?</string>
    <string name="prad_95">If you had to create a new type of sport where you have to be as slow as possible, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="prad_96">What\'s the most embarrassing time you tried to do something cool in front of your parents?</string>
    <string name="prad_97">If you could make a vegetable taste like a dessert, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="prad_98">What\'s the most absurd thing you\'ve done trying to avoid doing something important?</string>
    <string name="prad_99">If you had to create a new type of transportation that runs on emotion, how would it work?</string>
    <string name="premium">Premium</string>
    <string name="premium_access">ðŸŽ¯ Premium Access:</string>
    <string name="premium_access_label">ðŸŽ¯ Premium Access:</string>
    <string name="premium_access_lost">Premium Access Lost</string>
    <string name="premium_categories_locked">Premium categories locked</string>
    <string name="premium_categories_not_subscribed">Subscribe to unlock access to the collections below âœ¨</string>
    <string name="premium_categories_subscribed">All collections below are available to you with your subscription ðŸ’Ž</string>
    <string name="premium_content_unavailable">Premium content unavailable</string>
    <string name="premium_features_unlocked">All categories unlocked</string>
    <string name="premium_shared_message">%@ shared their Premium subscription with you!\n\nYou now have access to all premium features.</string>
    <string name="premium_unlimited">Go Premium to create unlimited memories with your partner</string>
    <string name="premium_unlocked">Premium unlocked!</string>
    <string name="preparation_in_progress">Preparing...</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="privacy_message">We promise to always keep your personal information private and secure.</string>
    <string name="privacy_promise">We promise to always keep your personal information private and secure.</string>
    <string name="private_answer_note">Your partner won\'t see your answer</string>
    <string name="product_loading_error">Error loading product</string>
    <string name="product_loading_failed">Product loading failed</string>
    <string name="product_not_available">Product not available</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="pud_10">What\'s one thing about yourself you\'d never want to change?</string>
    <string name="pud_100">Do you have pets? If so, which one?</string>
    <string name="pud_101">Would you rather have dogs or cats for the rest of your life?</string>
    <string name="pud_102">Do you believe in prophetic dreams?</string>
    <string name="pud_103">What do you prefer about me?</string>
    <string name="pud_104">What simple gesture do you think can convey a lot of love?</string>
    <string name="pud_105">What was the coolest trip you\'ve taken?</string>
    <string name="pud_106">Are you the type to make the first move?</string>
    <string name="pud_107">What\'s your definition of trust in a couple?</string>
    <string name="pud_108">Name a country you really dream of visiting.</string>
    <string name="pud_109">Are you more the type to open up easily or to take your time?</string>
    <string name="pud_11">When did you last have a serious relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_110">Do you prefer going camping or going out clubbing?</string>
    <string name="pud_111">What\'s one thing that always makes you angry?</string>
    <string name="pud_112">Do you have an anecdote you often tell?</string>
    <string name="pud_113">What\'s one thing you love about where you live?</string>
    <string name="pud_114">What\'s one thing you hate about where you live?</string>
    <string name="pud_115">What kind of simple moments make you deeply happy?</string>
    <string name="pud_116">Do you have a fear related to love that you\'d like to overcome?</string>
    <string name="pud_117">What\'s your way of seducing someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_118">If you could receive just one gift, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="pud_119">Do you prefer receiving a physical gift, a gift card, or money?</string>
    <string name="pud_12">Describe your love language to me.</string>
    <string name="pud_120">Would you describe yourself as introverted or extroverted?</string>
    <string name="pud_121">If you could relive one moment of your life, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="pud_122">How do you know you\'re falling in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_123">What can transform a beautiful encounter into a deep relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_124">Have you ever felt like someone could read you like an open book?</string>
    <string name="pud_125">What\'s something you feel but rarely express?</string>
    <string name="pud_126">What phrase once moved or deeply touched you?</string>
    <string name="pud_127">What\'s your favorite place to relax?</string>
    <string name="pud_128">Do you prefer going to the gym or working out at home?</string>
    <string name="pud_129">What\'s one thing a person could do to you that you could never forgive?</string>
    <string name="pud_13">What changed your view of relationships?</string>
    <string name="pud_130">Have you ever been betrayed by a friend?</string>
    <string name="pud_131">What do you prefer about your friends?</string>
    <string name="pud_132">How did you meet your best friend?</string>
    <string name="pud_133">Do you want children?</string>
    <string name="pud_134">What makes you want to have children?</string>
    <string name="pud_135">If you had to write an anonymous message to someone you love, what would you say and to whom would you send it?</string>
    <string name="pud_136">Do you want to get married?</string>
    <string name="pud_137">What\'s the biggest mistake or difficult situation you\'ve found yourself in?</string>
    <string name="pud_138">Do you prefer going on vacation to the beach or to a dynamic city?</string>
    <string name="pud_139">What\'s your dream car?</string>
    <string name="pud_14">If you had to leave tomorrow for a romantic trip, where would you go?</string>
    <string name="pud_140">What emotion do you feel most often when you\'re attracted to someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_141">What moment would you like to relive in slow motion?</string>
    <string name="pud_142">What\'s your favorite book?</string>
    <string name="pud_143">What\'s the worst movie you\'ve ever seen?</string>
    <string name="pud_144">What have you learned most valuable from your past relationships?</string>
    <string name="pud_145">What tiny detail can make you fall in love with someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_146">What superpower would you like to have?</string>
    <string name="pud_147">What\'s the most fun thing you\'ve done with your friends?</string>
    <string name="pud_148">Are you closer to your mother or your father?</string>
    <string name="pud_149">Who is your favorite family member?</string>
    <string name="pud_15">What\'s your biggest dream in life?</string>
    <string name="pud_150">What part of yourself would you like someone to really discover?</string>
    <string name="pud_151">What\'s the most impressive thing you\'ve ever done?</string>
    <string name="pud_152">What\'s your strangest habit?</string>
    <string name="pud_153">What emotion would you like to feel more in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_154">What\'s your biggest phobia?</string>
    <string name="pud_155">What\'s your most beautiful way of showing \'I care about you\' without words?</string>
    <string name="pud_156">What do you look forward to every year?</string>
    <string name="pud_157">Do you prefer winter or summer?</string>
    <string name="pud_158">Are you more attracted to actions, looks, or words?</string>
    <string name="pud_159">What\'s the promise you\'d like to make to your future love?</string>
    <string name="pud_16">What would you do differently in your last relationship, if you could?</string>
    <string name="pud_160">What\'s something that stressed you a lot but turned out to be unimportant?</string>
    <string name="pud_161">What do you think reveals a lot about a person you\'re dating?</string>
    <string name="pud_162">Have you ever had a crush on someone who didn\'t love you back?</string>
    <string name="pud_163">At what point do you know it\'s time to introduce someone to your family?</string>
    <string name="pud_164">Are you comfortable with silences when you\'re with someone you like?</string>
    <string name="pud_165">If you had a free day with nothing to do, how would you spend it?</string>
    <string name="pud_166">If your heart could speak, what would it say?</string>
    <string name="pud_167">Have you ever lost someone close to you?</string>
    <string name="pud_168">If you had three wishes, what would they be?</string>
    <string name="pud_169">What was your favorite cartoon when you were a child?</string>
    <string name="pud_17">What song touches your heart?</string>
    <string name="pud_170">What\'s the most disgusting thing you\'ve ever eaten?</string>
    <string name="pud_171">Do you prefer playing Truth or Dare?</string>
    <string name="pud_172">What\'s your favorite romantic ritual?</string>
    <string name="pud_173">Describe your perfect burger.</string>
    <string name="pud_174">Have you ever met a famous person?</string>
    <string name="pud_175">What song makes you want to fall in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_176">What part of yourself do you often keep for later in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_177">What makes you proud of your way of loving?</string>
    <string name="pud_178">Have you ever loved someone in secret?</string>
    <string name="pud_179">Do you think you\'re a competitive person?</string>
    <string name="pud_18">If you could invite anyone in the world to dinner, who would you choose?</string>
    <string name="pud_180">What romantic movie scene makes you dream?</string>
    <string name="pud_181">What\'s your favorite restaurant?</string>
    <string name="pud_182">What makes you want to kiss someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_183">What moment from your past would you do differently?</string>
    <string name="pud_184">Is there a song that always reminds you of memories?</string>
    <string name="pud_185">If you had to listen to one song on repeat, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="pud_186">What\'s something everyone should experience at least once in their life?</string>
    <string name="pud_187">Are you looking for intensity or security in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_188">What would be the most romantic trip according to you?</string>
    <string name="pud_189">Would you rather go skiing or surfing?</string>
    <string name="pud_19">Before making a phone call, do you ever rehearse what you\'re going to say? Why?</string>
    <string name="pud_190">What romantic nickname do you prefer most?</string>
    <string name="pud_191">What do you never want to forget in a love story?</string>
    <string name="pud_192">What does a healthy beginning of love look like to you?</string>
    <string name="pud_193">What image do you have of yourself in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_194">What celebrity would be the worst person for a dinner according to you?</string>
    <string name="pud_195">Are you more into declarations or discreet gestures in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_196">What combination of flavors is a bit weird but you love it?</string>
    <string name="pud_197">What\'s your most precious possession?</string>
    <string name="pud_198">What\'s something you never get tired of?</string>
    <string name="pud_199">Who is your favorite comedian?</string>
    <string name="pud_2">What rare quality in someone immediately attracts you?</string>
    <string name="pud_20">Do you really believe in love at first sight?</string>
    <string name="pud_200">What series do you love that would surprise people if they knew?</string>
    <string name="pud_201">What\'s your favorite series of all time?</string>
    <string name="pud_202">If you had to choose, would you prefer Instagram or TikTok?</string>
    <string name="pud_203">Is there a song that makes you think of a particular person?</string>
    <string name="pud_204">What truth about yourself would you like the other person to discover naturally?</string>
    <string name="pud_205">What do you know you\'re a bit (or very) judgmental about?</string>
    <string name="pud_206">What ice cream flavor would you eat every day if you could?</string>
    <string name="pud_207">Have you ever loved someone who was nothing like you?</string>
    <string name="pud_208">What\'s something illegal that you think should be legalized?</string>
    <string name="pud_209">What\'s your favorite part of each day?</string>
    <string name="pud_21">What would a \'perfect\' day look like for you?</string>
    <string name="pud_210">Would you rather give up coffee or alcohol?</string>
    <string name="pud_211">What helps you know if a person is right for you?</string>
    <string name="pud_212">What do you think is the most romantic movie?</string>
    <string name="pud_213">What age have you preferred so far in your life?</string>
    <string name="pud_214">What makes you feel really listened to?</string>
    <string name="pud_215">Have you ever been surprised by your own feelings?</string>
    <string name="pud_216">What does a healthy relationship represent for you today?</string>
    <string name="pud_217">How old were you during your best birthday?</string>
    <string name="pud_218">What part of yourself would you like to offer unreservedly to someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_219">What celebrity was your very first crush?</string>
    <string name="pud_22">When did you last sing? For yourself? For someone else?</string>
    <string name="pud_220">What\'s the small detail on a date that changes everything for you?</string>
    <string name="pud_221">What\'s your definition of \'connection\' between two people?</string>
    <string name="pud_222">How old were you during your first kiss?</string>
    <string name="pud_223">How do you know you really, really love someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_224">Are you the type to project quickly or to savor the present moment?</string>
    <string name="pud_225">What\'s the most useful skill you\'ve ever learned?</string>
    <string name="pud_226">What soothes you in a human presence?</string>
    <string name="pud_227">Is there a phrase you\'d like to hear after a first date?</string>
    <string name="pud_228">What\'s your biggest wish for your future self?</string>
    <string name="pud_229">If you had to offer an unforgettable memory to someone, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="pud_23">Do you have a secret feeling about how you\'re going to die?</string>
    <string name="pud_230">What\'s your favorite way to say \'you matter to me\'?</string>
    <string name="pud_231">What\'s a temptation you can never resist?</string>
    <string name="pud_232">What\'s your least favorite current fashion trend?</string>
    <string name="pud_233">What\'s your favorite store for shopping?</string>
    <string name="pud_234">What\'s the story you always tell that makes everyone laugh?</string>
    <string name="pud_235">What question would you like to ask someone without filter?</string>
    <string name="pud_236">What do you do every night before going to bed?</string>
    <string name="pud_237">Would you say you\'re more of a night owl or an early bird?</string>
    <string name="pud_238">If you could time travel, what decade would you like to live in?</string>
    <string name="pud_239">What do you miss most about your childhood?</string>
    <string name="pud_24">What in your life do you feel most grateful for?</string>
    <string name="pud_240">What\'s the most beautiful memory you have with your father?</string>
    <string name="pud_241">What\'s the most beautiful memory you have with your mother?</string>
    <string name="pud_242">Who is your favorite fictional villain?</string>
    <string name="pud_243">Do you prefer watching an action/adventure movie or a comedy?</string>
    <string name="pud_244">What\'s your favorite holiday?</string>
    <string name="pud_245">What\'s the dish you can really cook well?</string>
    <string name="pud_246">What\'s the dish you\'d really like to know how to cook?</string>
    <string name="pud_247">What meal comforts you most when you\'re having a bad day?</string>
    <string name="pud_248">What\'s your definition of a healthy relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_249">What always makes you feel like a child?</string>
    <string name="pud_25">If you could change something about the way you were raised, what would you change?</string>
    <string name="pud_250">If you were a ghost, who would you haunt?</string>
    <string name="pud_251">If you had to choose one emotion to relive over and over, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="pud_252">Are you more attracted to intensity or consistency in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_253">Do you think ghosts exist?</string>
    <string name="pud_254">What\'s your favorite thing to do on vacation?</string>
    <string name="pud_255">Do you prefer to relax on vacation or go exploring and having adventures?</string>
    <string name="pud_256">What\'s something you\'d like to be able to do every morning but never have time for?</string>
    <string name="pud_26">If you could wake up tomorrow having gained one quality or skill, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="pud_27">Is there something you\'ve been dreaming of doing for a long time? Why haven\'t you done it yet?</string>
    <string name="pud_28">What\'s your life\'s greatest accomplishment?</string>
    <string name="pud_29">What\'s your most painful memory?</string>
    <string name="pud_3">Is there a childhood memory you\'d like to relive today?</string>
    <string name="pud_30">If you knew you were going to die suddenly in a year, would you change anything about the way you\'re currently living? Why?</string>
    <string name="pud_31">Are you more passionate or logical in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_32">What\'s the first thing you notice about someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_33">What\'s your idea of a perfect evening for two?</string>
    <string name="pud_34">Have you ever had your heart broken?</string>
    <string name="pud_35">What personality trait makes you melt for someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_36">What role do love and affection play in your life?</string>
    <string name="pud_37">What\'s the most important thing when making a first impression?</string>
    <string name="pud_38">How close and warm is your family? Do you think your childhood was happier than most people\'s?</string>
    <string name="pud_39">How do you feel about your relationship with your mother?</string>
    <string name="pud_4">Who is the person you\'re closest to in your life, and why?</string>
    <string name="pud_40">How do you feel about your relationship with your father?</string>
    <string name="pud_41">Do you believe in soulmates?</string>
    <string name="pud_42">What makes someone unforgettable in your opinion?</string>
    <string name="pud_43">Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share...</string>
    <string name="pud_44">What\'s your biggest expectation in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_45">What movie or series makes you want to be in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_46">Do you prefer discreet or grand declarations?</string>
    <string name="pud_47">When did you last cry in front of someone? And alone?</string>
    <string name="pud_48">Is there something you think should never be joked about?</string>
    <string name="pud_49">If you were to die tonight without the possibility of speaking to anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven\'t you told them yet?</string>
    <string name="pud_5">What are you most proud of, even if you rarely talk about it?</string>
    <string name="pud_50">Have you ever felt an immediate connection with someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_51">What do you feel when you fall in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_52">If you could relive one year of your life, what age would you choose?</string>
    <string name="pud_53">Are you the type of person who believes in signs of destiny?</string>
    <string name="pud_54">What kind of compliment really touches you?</string>
    <string name="pud_55">If you had to sum up love in one word, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="pud_56">What other job do you think you would love to do?</string>
    <string name="pud_57">What do you attribute your greatest successes in life to? And your greatest failures?</string>
    <string name="pud_58">If you could only eat one meal for the rest of your life, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="pud_59">If safety wasn\'t a concern, what natural phenomenon or disaster would you like to experience?</string>
    <string name="pud_6">Do you think people enter your life for a reason?</string>
    <string name="pud_60">What question would you like to ask someone before falling in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_61">What\'s your favorite way to show affection?</string>
    <string name="pud_62">Who is a person in your life that you deeply respect? Why?</string>
    <string name="pud_63">If you had to choose one sentence as a life mantra, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="pud_64">What\'s something you\'re happy to never have to do again?</string>
    <string name="pud_65">What kind of moments strengthen the bond between two people in your opinion?</string>
    <string name="pud_66">Your house is on fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to grab one object. Which one? Why?</string>
    <string name="pud_67">What do you feel you are best at?</string>
    <string name="pud_68">What do you expect from an ideal first date?</string>
    <string name="pud_69">If you could change one thing about your appearance, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="pud_7">Is there a question you\'re trying to answer right now in your life?</string>
    <string name="pud_70">What makes you say: \'This is the right person\'?</string>
    <string name="pud_71">Do you prefer meaningful glances or long conversations?</string>
    <string name="pud_72">How do you behave when you fall in love?</string>
    <string name="pud_73">What new hobby would you like to try?</string>
    <string name="pud_74">Do you play video games? If so, which one?</string>
    <string name="pud_75">Are you more of a long messages or spontaneous calls person?</string>
    <string name="pud_76">What do you think makes a relationship last?</string>
    <string name="pud_77">What part of your body do you like most physically?</string>
    <string name="pud_78">What\'s one of your favorite childhood memories?</string>
    <string name="pud_79">If you could live anywhere in the world for a year, where would you go?</string>
    <string name="pud_8">Is there a moment you\'d like to go back and change?</string>
    <string name="pud_80">Have you ever experienced a moment that seemed straight out of a movie?</string>
    <string name="pud_81">If you could have a superpower, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="pud_82">If love were a season, which would best represent you?</string>
    <string name="pud_83">What type of love language seduces you most in someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_84">Do you think you\'d make a good food critic?</string>
    <string name="pud_85">If you could meet a celebrity, living or dead, who would you choose?</string>
    <string name="pud_86">What\'s the smallest detail that can change everything on a date?</string>
    <string name="pud_87">Which of your parents do you most resemble?</string>
    <string name="pud_88">Do you have a vision of love that has changed over time?</string>
    <string name="pud_89">How would you like to be remembered after your death?</string>
    <string name="pud_9">If you had to describe a balanced relationship in three words, what would they be?</string>
    <string name="pud_90">What do you believe you\'re capable of in your life?</string>
    <string name="pud_91">What values are essential to you in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="pud_92">Who is your favorite person to follow on Instagram?</string>
    <string name="pud_93">What\'s one thing a person can do to instantly impress you?</string>
    <string name="pud_94">Do you have a secret you dream of one day sharing with the right person?</string>
    <string name="pud_95">What kind of connection are you looking for with someone?</string>
    <string name="pud_96">What do you think is the most beautiful beginning?</string>
    <string name="pud_97">What\'s your favorite compliment to receive?</string>
    <string name="pud_98">What makes you smile, even on a very bad day?</string>
    <string name="pud_99">Do you have a phrase or idea you\'d like people to remember about you?</string>
    <string name="purchase_cancelled">Purchase cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="purchase_error">Purchase error</string>
    <string name="purchases_not_allowed">Purchases are not allowed on this device</string>
    <string name="purchases_not_authorized">Purchases are not authorized on this device</string>
    <string name="qp_10">Do you think you can be friends with someone you\'re attracted to?</string>
    <string name="qp_100">If you could show your inner world in images, what would it look like?</string>
    <string name="qp_101">Do you think you have self-confidence?</string>
    <string name="qp_102">What injustice have you experienced that you\'ve never forgotten?</string>
    <string name="qp_103">Do you think the universe gives us what we deserve?</string>
    <string name="qp_104">Do you think life is fair or unfair?</string>
    <string name="qp_105">Do you think the experiences we live are there to teach us things we need to learn?</string>
    <string name="qp_106">Have you ever felt like no one really understood you?</string>
    <string name="qp_107">If you could repair just one thing from your past, what would you change as a priority?</string>
    <string name="qp_108">Do you think the music we listen to can influence our mood?</string>
    <string name="qp_109">When was the last time you were angry at yourself? And why?</string>
    <string name="qp_11">What emotional wound are you still trying to heal today?</string>
    <string name="qp_110">What\'s something you\'d like to improve about yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_111">What do you feel when you\'re facing your reflection in the mirror?</string>
    <string name="qp_112">What do you think about the world of workâ€”do you feel it\'s made for you?</string>
    <string name="qp_113">What would you have liked to hear more often in your childhood?</string>
    <string name="qp_114">What impact does the parent/child relationship have on an adult\'s life according to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_115">If you had children, what\'s the first thing you would teach them?</string>
    <string name="qp_116">Do you think you\'re fully exploiting your potential?</string>
    <string name="qp_117">What do you think about new generations? Was it better before?</string>
    <string name="qp_118">What\'s more important in a couple according to you, love or honesty?</string>
    <string name="qp_119">Would you describe yourself as someone sensitive?</string>
    <string name="qp_12">Is there a moment in your life when you felt completely lost?</string>
    <string name="qp_120">If you had to choose one word to summarize your past, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="qp_121">What\'s the greatest life lesson you learned last year?</string>
    <string name="qp_122">What\'s something you\'d like to leave behind once and for all?</string>
    <string name="qp_123">Would you like to change your current life? If yes, what bothers you most today?</string>
    <string name="qp_124">Do you ever find yourself feeling depressed?</string>
    <string name="qp_125">What pain have you normalized over time?</string>
    <string name="qp_126">Who is the person who makes you happiest right now?</string>
    <string name="qp_127">Do you think sessions with a psychologist would do you good?</string>
    <string name="qp_128">What\'s your way of getting through your inner storms?</string>
    <string name="qp_129">Are your thoughts more often on your side, or against you?</string>
    <string name="qp_13">What person has had the greatest impact on your life?</string>
    <string name="qp_130">Do you consider yourself someone who has succeeded?</string>
    <string name="qp_131">How have your parents influenced your vision of love and relationships?</string>
    <string name="qp_132">What do you think happens after death?</string>
    <string name="qp_133">Do you think lying can be acceptable? In what cases?</string>
    <string name="qp_134">What\'s something you had never noticed about yourself before someone pointed it out?</string>
    <string name="qp_135">Does the fact of aging scare you?</string>
    <string name="qp_136">If we ever argue by message, do you prefer to resolve it right away or wait to see each other face to face?</string>
    <string name="qp_137">How did others treat you in high school?</string>
    <string name="qp_138">Would you be ready to give up some of your dreams or professional goals for love?</string>
    <string name="qp_139">Would you tell me if I said or did something that hurt you?</string>
    <string name="qp_14">If there was a subject to remove from school, which would you choose, and what would you replace it with? Why?</string>
    <string name="qp_140">How do you cope with difficult moments?</string>
    <string name="qp_141">Do you believe in love at first sight?</string>
    <string name="qp_142">Where should we go on vacation next time?</string>
    <string name="qp_143">What do you like about being in a relationship with me?</string>
    <string name="qp_144">Do you feel like you\'ve become a better version of yourself over time?</string>
    <string name="qp_145">Do we spend enough time together according to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_146">Have you ever felt like you were running late on your own life?</string>
    <string name="qp_147">Do you think spending time together is as important as spending time apart?</string>
    <string name="qp_148">What\'s the phrase that could summarize what you\'re feeling right now?</string>
    <string name="qp_149">Do you have a belief that keeps you standing despite everything?</string>
    <string name="qp_15">What have you never dared to say to your parents, but wish you had?</string>
    <string name="qp_150">If someone entered your inner world, what would they discover first?</string>
    <string name="qp_151">Do you feel heard when we\'re together?</string>
    <string name="qp_152">What part of you would you like to see evolve in the coming years?</string>
    <string name="qp_153">Do you think jealousy is proof of love in a couple?</string>
    <string name="qp_154">Are you the same person as 5 years ago? If not, what has changed about you since?</string>
    <string name="qp_155">What habit protects you but might prevent you from moving forward?</string>
    <string name="qp_156">If you could ask your future self a question, what would you ask?</string>
    <string name="qp_157">Do you prefer planned or impromptu romantic evenings?</string>
    <string name="qp_158">According to you, how can we keep the flame alive in our relationship?</string>
    <string name="qp_159">Do you believe in destiny?</string>
    <string name="qp_16">In your opinion, what will matter most for our society in the next 50 years: preserving our traditions or changing them?</string>
    <string name="qp_160">Do you have confidence when you think about your future?</string>
    <string name="qp_161">How would you describe your love language to a stranger?</string>
    <string name="qp_162">Do you think some people are made for each other?</string>
    <string name="qp_163">If you and I were proof of something, what would we be proof of?</string>
    <string name="qp_164">What\'s your favorite movie for a romantic evening?</string>
    <string name="qp_165">Can you really keep a secret?</string>
    <string name="qp_166">What do you think about public displays of affection?</string>
    <string name="qp_167">Do you wish to get married someday?</string>
    <string name="qp_168">What do you think about solitude? Is it the same as isolation, in your view?</string>
    <string name="qp_169">Have you ever needed to take a step back so you wouldn\'t lose yourself in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="qp_17">What have you learned about yourself through love?</string>
    <string name="qp_170">How do you describe me to your friends?</string>
    <string name="qp_171">Is there something I used to do that you miss now?</string>
    <string name="qp_172">What does falling in love mean to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_173">How would you tell our love story?</string>
    <string name="qp_174">What do you value most in a relationship?</string>
    <string name="qp_175">Have you ever changed for someone else, to the point of not recognizing yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_176">When you\'re having a bad day, what can I do to help you feel better?</string>
    <string name="qp_177">Do you believe in soulmates?</string>
    <string name="qp_178">Do you think negative experiences can transform us into better people?</string>
    <string name="qp_179">What are things you wish you had learned earlier in life?</string>
    <string name="qp_18">What would you like to be remembered for after your death?</string>
    <string name="qp_180">When did you feel you were starting to fall in love with me?</string>
    <string name="qp_181">What\'s the most memorable gesture I\'ve made for you?</string>
    <string name="qp_182">What\'s the part of your story you rarely tell?</string>
    <string name="qp_183">What moment of your life would deserve to be told in a book?</string>
    <string name="qp_184">What are truly romantic vacations for you?</string>
    <string name="qp_185">What promise did you once make but didn\'t keep? And why?</string>
    <string name="qp_186">How do you imagine our future together?</string>
    <string name="qp_187">What\'s your favorite part of our relationship? And the one you like least?</string>
    <string name="qp_188">Have you ever lied to me when answering these questions?</string>
    <string name="qp_189">Have you ever run away from a situation? How did it go?</string>
    <string name="qp_19">What\'s the biggest mistake you\'ve made that taught you something?</string>
    <string name="qp_190">Are there signs that show you\'re not doing well, that I should learn to recognize?</string>
    <string name="qp_191">What do you prefer about yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_192">How do you let off steam or release pressure?</string>
    <string name="qp_193">Are there specific qualities you look for in your friends?</string>
    <string name="qp_194">How do you define a solid relationship?</string>
    <string name="qp_195">What emotion have you learned to hide over time?</string>
    <string name="qp_196">If you could live one moment again, without changing it, which would you choose?</string>
    <string name="qp_197">Do you think it\'s important to wear a mask in public or should we be fully ourselves?</string>
    <string name="qp_198">What\'s the most beautiful compliment I could give you?</string>
    <string name="qp_199">Do you think I\'m grateful enough with you? And do I show it?</string>
    <string name="qp_2">If you could free yourself from an inner burden today, which one would you choose?</string>
    <string name="qp_20">Who was the person in your past who turned into a lesson?</string>
    <string name="qp_200">What importance do you place on family?</string>
    <string name="qp_201">What importance do you place on religion?</string>
    <string name="qp_202">Do you prefer a lie that feels good or a truth that hurts?</string>
    <string name="qp_203">What wound has shaped part of your personality?</string>
    <string name="qp_204">What would you like to pass on to a child you would raise?</string>
    <string name="qp_205">Have you ever given up a relationship out of love for yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_206">Do you feel like I prevent you from doing certain things? If yes, do you think it\'s a good thing?</string>
    <string name="qp_207">Do you believe in luck?</string>
    <string name="qp_208">How would your exes describe you?</string>
    <string name="qp_209">What forms of non-sexual intimacy do you particularly appreciate?</string>
    <string name="qp_21">When was the last time you felt ashamed?</string>
    <string name="qp_210">Do you want to live in another city someday?</string>
    <string name="qp_211">For you, when do you know it\'s time to break up with someone?</string>
    <string name="qp_212">What are your reflexes when you\'re stressed?</string>
    <string name="qp_213">If you could write a letter to your future self, what would it contain?</string>
    <string name="qp_214">What\'s the most meaningful conversation you\'ve had?</string>
    <string name="qp_215">Do you consider yourself a good person?</string>
    <string name="qp_216">What\'s your defense mechanism that few people notice?</string>
    <string name="qp_217">What do you feel when you look at the sky at night?</string>
    <string name="qp_218">Have you ever wanted to disappear to see who would look for you first?</string>
    <string name="qp_219">What ordinary thing touches you deeply without you knowing why?</string>
    <string name="qp_22">If there\'s one year of your life you could relive over and over, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="qp_220">Do you think mistakes are important for one\'s own development?</string>
    <string name="qp_221">What do you hope from yourself for the coming years?</string>
    <string name="qp_222">Who was the most benevolent person with you during your childhood?</string>
    <string name="qp_223">How would you describe your relationship with your grandparents?</string>
    <string name="qp_224">What\'s most important in a couple according to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_225">What quality should a man have according to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_226">What quality should a woman have according to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_227">Do you often need to spend time alone, just with yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_228">What do you think about vulgarity in a couple?</string>
    <string name="qp_229">Do you think our ancestors watch over us?</string>
    <string name="qp_23">What character trait from your childhood have you kept until today?</string>
    <string name="qp_230">What\'s the historical event you like most?</string>
    <string name="qp_231">Have you ever loved someone with a love you didn\'t understand yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_232">Do you feel at peace with your past?</string>
    <string name="qp_233">If you had past demons to fight, could you describe them to me?</string>
    <string name="qp_234">If you had to describe yourself to a stranger but without any filter, what would you say?</string>
    <string name="qp_235">What truth do you want to scream but still keep inside you?</string>
    <string name="qp_236">What about you deserves to be recognized more?</string>
    <string name="qp_237">Do you feel understood by your parents?</string>
    <string name="qp_238">Who\'s the last person you were afraid of losing?</string>
    <string name="qp_239">Describe what I could do to make you even happier</string>
    <string name="qp_24">What do you think about astrology and horoscopes?</string>
    <string name="qp_240">What would you like people to finally understand about you?</string>
    <string name="qp_241">What\'s the question you often ask others but avoid yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_242">What\'s the most beautiful risk you\'ve taken in your life?</string>
    <string name="qp_243">Have you ever felt a love stronger than reason?</string>
    <string name="qp_244">Do you think love is essential to have a fulfilling life?</string>
    <string name="qp_245">What would you like to learn to love about yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_246">Are you proud of the person you\'re becoming?</string>
    <string name="qp_247">What could we do together to help us understand each other even better?</string>
    <string name="qp_248">If you could give advice to all the teenagers in the world, what would you say?</string>
    <string name="qp_249">What do you respect most about me?</string>
    <string name="qp_25">What is the thing you are most proud of about yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_250">If you had the power to change one thing in this world, what would you change?</string>
    <string name="qp_251">Do you think shared moments of silence in a couple are important?</string>
    <string name="qp_252">What\'s the part of you that has evolved most in recent years?</string>
    <string name="qp_253">Do you think boredom is a good thing for a child\'s development?</string>
    <string name="qp_254">What could emotionally free you if you finally expressed it?</string>
    <string name="qp_255">Have you ever felt like your heart spoke a language no one understood?</string>
    <string name="qp_256">What\'s the question you\'d never want to be asked? Why?</string>
    <string name="qp_26">What aspect of yourself makes you suffer most in silence?</string>
    <string name="qp_27">What inner battle are you fighting without telling anyone?</string>
    <string name="qp_28">What does friendship represent to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_29">What do you think about male/female friendship? Is it sincerely possible?</string>
    <string name="qp_3">In your opinion, have the Internet, smartphones, and new technologies made the world better or worse?</string>
    <string name="qp_30">Looking back over the past ten years, how have you changed? And are you happy with this evolution?</string>
    <string name="qp_31">How would you like to feel in ten years, emotionally or internally?</string>
    <string name="qp_32">What is your greatest success, and your biggest failure?</string>
    <string name="qp_33">Who has had the greatest impact on the way you see life?</string>
    <string name="qp_34">What mistake taught you the most in life?</string>
    <string name="qp_35">What do you really expect from a romantic relationship?</string>
    <string name="qp_36">How would you like to be seen or perceived by others?</string>
    <string name="qp_37">What are the biggest challenges you\'re going through right now?</string>
    <string name="qp_38">Have you ever been your own enemy? In what context?</string>
    <string name="qp_39">Is there something you dream of doing, but don\'t dare to start?</string>
    <string name="qp_4">What truth about yourself still scares you a bit to face?</string>
    <string name="qp_40">What are you most grateful for in your life today?</string>
    <string name="qp_41">Is there a subject or concept you have trouble understanding or even imagining?</string>
    <string name="qp_42">What truth do you refuse to admit about yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_43">How do you handle your moments of sadness?</string>
    <string name="qp_44">What is the memory that has marked you the most with your father or mother?</string>
    <string name="qp_45">If you could erase one memory, which would it be?</string>
    <string name="qp_46">How do you define success? And when did you feel you had truly succeeded?</string>
    <string name="qp_47">What difficult choice have you had to make in your life?</string>
    <string name="qp_48">What annoys you or easily makes you angry?</string>
    <string name="qp_49">What quest or goal obsessed you for a long time, but you eventually gave up?</string>
    <string name="qp_5">How would your life be different if you had been born as the other gender?</string>
    <string name="qp_50">What occupies your mind and sometimes prevents you from sleeping?</string>
    <string name="qp_51">Do you think you truly know yourself?</string>
    <string name="qp_52">What does true love mean to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_53">Is there a character trait in me that you don\'t yet understand, but would like to?</string>
    <string name="qp_54">How has your first impression of me changed since we met?</string>
    <string name="qp_55">What is something your parents did that you refuse to repeat in your own life?</string>
    <string name="qp_56">In your opinion, what does it mean to succeed in life?</string>
    <string name="qp_57">What did you lack most in your childhood?</string>
    <string name="qp_58">What made you want to seek a relationship?</string>
    <string name="qp_59">Do you think the length of a relationship makes it easier to forgive infidelity?</string>
    <string name="qp_6">What part of your past have you learned to love, despite the pain?</string>
    <string name="qp_60">Do you think you have changed since we became a couple? And do you think these changes are positive?</string>
    <string name="qp_61">In your opinion, what are the three biggest things we have in common?</string>
    <string name="qp_62">In your opinion, what is our biggest difference?</string>
    <string name="qp_63">Do you believe some things are written in advance, like destiny?</string>
    <string name="qp_64">What do you feel when you think about the future? Do you feel stressed?</string>
    <string name="qp_65">Are you someone who\'s afraid of others\' judgment?</string>
    <string name="qp_66">What moment we lived together still makes you smile? What made it so special?</string>
    <string name="qp_67">In a relationship, what space of freedom is essential for you?</string>
    <string name="qp_68">What\'s your definition of inner peace?</string>
    <string name="qp_69">Do you consider us as a family? If not, what does family represent to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_7">What do you hide behind the mask you wear in public?</string>
    <string name="qp_70">What\'s the moment when you felt like you were reborn?</string>
    <string name="qp_71">Have you ever been afraid of loving too hard?</string>
    <string name="qp_72">Surprise me: tell me something about yourself that I don\'t know yet.</string>
    <string name="qp_73">What\'s the message you would give to all of humanity if you had a giant microphone?</string>
    <string name="qp_74">Name three things that happened to you last week for which you feel gratitude.</string>
    <string name="qp_75">Are you more of a giver, receiver, or a balance between both? What influences your behavior?</string>
    <string name="qp_76">What are five important things you\'d like to accomplish before you die?</string>
    <string name="qp_77">What makes you cry but you hide from others?</string>
    <string name="qp_78">Who do you really trust around you today?</string>
    <string name="qp_79">What emotion crosses you most often these days?</string>
    <string name="qp_8">What buried emotion still tries to resurface sometimes?</string>
    <string name="qp_80">What role does communication play in a couple according to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_81">If you could press a \'life reset\' button, would you do it?</string>
    <string name="qp_82">What\'s something you know to be true, even if you can\'t prove it?</string>
    <string name="qp_83">If you could travel through time, what era would you go to?</string>
    <string name="qp_84">Can you tell me the story of your life in 4 minutes, with as much detail as possible?</string>
    <string name="qp_85">What\'s the thought that comes back most often when you\'re alone?</string>
    <string name="qp_86">Have you ever felt like you didn\'t deserve to be loved?</string>
    <string name="qp_87">How about we each share three qualities we see in each other?</string>
    <string name="qp_88">What was your favorite place as a child, and what made it special?</string>
    <string name="qp_89">If your heart could speak, what would it say?</string>
    <string name="qp_9">If you had to start your life over tomorrow, what would you do differently from the beginning?</string>
    <string name="qp_90">Who is the person you admire most?</string>
    <string name="qp_91">Is there a period of your life you\'d like to relive to repair it?</string>
    <string name="qp_92">What would a truly perfect day look like for you?</string>
    <string name="qp_93">If you had â‚¬100,000 to give to a cause, which would you choose, and why?</string>
    <string name="qp_94">Tell me about a day you\'ll never forgetâ€”whether it was good or bad.</string>
    <string name="qp_95">Do you think your entourage really understands you?</string>
    <string name="qp_96">What\'s the thing that gives you most pleasure when someone says it to you?</string>
    <string name="qp_97">How would you describe emotional intelligence?</string>
    <string name="qp_98">Who is the person you count on most?</string>
    <string name="qp_99">If you had a diary, what would you write on the first page?</string>
    <string name="questions_answered">Questions\nanswered</string>
    <string name="questions_cached">Questions cached</string>
    <string name="questions_intro_subtitle">Behind every argument often lies a lack of communication. That\'s why we\'ve designed simple yet deep questions, meant to strengthen your bond even more.</string>
    <string name="questions_intro_title">Questions designed to bring you closer.</string>
    <string name="quick_actions">âš¡ï¸ Quick Actions</string>
    <string name="real_time_distance">Real-time distance</string>
    <string name="receipt_validation_failed">Receipt validation failed</string>
    <string name="recover_access_message">Recover your access to all other questions and categories</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="relationship_duration_question">How long have you been together?</string>
    <string name="relationship_goals_question">What are your relationship goals?</string>
    <string name="relationship_improvement_question">What would you like to improve in your relationship?</string>
    <string name="reload_cache">Reload cache</string>
    <string name="remaining_entries">Only</string>
    <string name="remaining_entries_message">Only %d %@ entr%@ remaining!</string>
    <string name="remove_1_favorite">Remove 1 favorite</string>
    <string name="requires_subscription">Requires subscription</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="response_answered">Answered</string>
    <string name="response_skipped">Skipped</string>
    <string name="response_waiting">Waiting</string>
    <string name="restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="restore_error">Restore error</string>
    <string name="restricted">Restricted</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="save_challenge_button">Sauvegarder le dÃ©fi</string>
    <string name="save_moments_together">Save your favorite moments together</string>
    <string name="saved_challenges_title">DÃ©fis sauvegardÃ©s</string>
    <string name="saving">Saving...</string>
    <string name="search_description">Search for \'Love2Love\', then pick the widget you want.</string>
    <string name="search_home_description">Search for \'Love2Love\', then pick the widget you want.</string>
    <string name="search_love2love">Search love2love</string>
    <string name="search_love2love_home">Search Love2Love</string>
    <string name="search_placeholder">Search...</string>
    <string name="seconds">seconds</string>
    <string name="secure_account">SECURE YOUR ACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>
    <string name="select_allow_when_active">Select Allow When App is Active</string>
    <string name="select_lock_screen">Select your lock screen</string>
    <string name="select_more_photos">You can select more photos in Settings</string>
    <string name="select_more_photos_settings">You can select more photos in Settings</string>
    <string name="select_photo">Select photo</string>
    <string name="selected_location">Selected location</string>
    <string name="selected_location_custom">Selected location</string>
    <string name="send_code">Send code</string>
    <string name="send_code_to_partner">Send this code to your partner</string>
    <string name="send_partner_code">Send partner code</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_button">Settings</string>
    <string name="share_partner_code_message">Here is my Love2Love partner code: {code}</string>
    <string name="shared_favorite_questions">Shared favorite questions</string>
    <string name="shared_journal">Shared journal</string>
    <string name="shared_premium">Shared Premium subscription</string>
    <string name="sign_in_apple">Continue with Apple</string>
    <string name="simulate_partner_connection">Simulate partner connection</string>
    <string name="simulate_revocation">âŒ Simulate Revocation</string>
    <string name="simulate_subscription">Simulate Subscription</string>
    <string name="since_date">Since</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="skip_notifications">Skip this step</string>
    <string name="skip_step">Skip this step</string>
    <string name="start_free">Try For Free</string>
    <string name="start_trial">START TRIAL</string>
    <string name="weekly_plan">Weekly</string>
    <string name="monthly_plan">Monthly</string>
    <string name="weekly_price_description">%1$s per week</string>
    <string name="monthly_price_description">%1$s per month after free trial</string>
    <string name="save_percentage">Save 20%</string>
    <string name="status_active">Active</string>
    <string name="status_both_answered">Both responded</string>
    <string name="status_expired">Expired</string>
    <string name="status_one_answered">One response received</string>
    <string name="status_pending">Waiting for responses</string>
    <string name="status_skipped">Skipped</string>
    <string name="step_counter">Step %d of %d</string>
    <string name="subscribe">Subscribe</string>
    <string name="subscribe_access_questions">Subscribe to access all questions</string>
    <string name="subscribe_button">Subscribe</string>
    <string name="subscription_revoked_message">%@ cancelled their Premium subscription.\n\nYou now only have access to free features.</string>
    <string name="subscription_subtitle">Your partner won\'t have to pay anything</string>
    <string name="subscription_title">Choose your plan</string>
    <string name="surprise">surprise</string>
    <string name="swipe_description">Swipe down to show your lock screen, then press and hold.</string>
    <string name="swipe_down">Swipe down</string>
    <string name="syncing">Syncing...</string>
    <string name="tap_authorize">Tap on Authorize</string>
    <string name="tap_customize">Tap the Customize button</string>
    <string name="tap_on_me">Tap on</string>
    <string name="tap_plus_button">Tap the + button</string>
    <string name="tap_to_unlock">Tap to unlock</string>
    <string name="tap_unlock_surprise">Tap on me to unlock a surprise</string>
    <string name="terms">Terms</string>
    <string name="test_actions">âš¡ï¸ Test Actions</string>
    <string name="thank_you">Thank you for</string>
    <string name="thank_you_for">Thank you for</string>
    <string name="thinking_of_you">I\'m thinking of you</string>
    <string name="time_hours_ago">%d hours ago</string>
    <string name="time_minutes_ago">%d min ago</string>
    <string name="time_now">Now</string>
    <string name="time_together">Time together</string>
    <string name="together">together</string>
    <string name="token_serialization_error">Token serialization error</string>
    <string name="tp_10">Would you rather relive your first conversation or your first look?</string>
    <string name="tp_100">Would you rather have a relationship at 100 mph or one that takes all its time (sometimes too much)?</string>
    <string name="tp_101">Would you rather discover a painful truth about someone you love or live in a comfortable illusion?</string>
    <string name="tp_102">Would you rather have a silent but deep love, or a talkative but chaotic love?</string>
    <string name="tp_103">Would you rather have a partner who\'s always predictable or always (too) surprising?</string>
    <string name="tp_104">Would you rather be popular with many superficial acquaintances or have few friends but deep connections?</string>
    <string name="tp_105">Would you rather laugh every day with the other or cry once from intense happiness?</string>
    <string name="tp_106">Would you rather have a deep conversation with a stranger or a light conversation with your best friend?</string>
    <string name="tp_107">Would you rather be the one who always listens to others\' problems or the one who always needs to confide?</string>
    <string name="tp_108">Would you rather directly confront someone talking behind your back or ignore them and move on?</string>
    <string name="tp_109">Would you rather understand the meaning of the universe or know the secret to personal happiness?</string>
    <string name="tp_11">Would you rather spend 5 years in prison or 10 years in a coma?</string>
    <string name="tp_110">Would you rather be able to taste every flavor in the world, or hear every piece of music ever composed?</string>
    <string name="tp_111">Would you rather perfectly understand how the human brain works or perfectly understand artificial intelligence?</string>
    <string name="tp_112">Would you rather I understand you without a word or listen to you for hours?</string>
    <string name="tp_113">Would you rather discover a major historical secret or invent revolutionary technology?</string>
    <string name="tp_114">Would you rather live in a world without diseases but where emotions are suppressed, or in our current world with its joys and sorrows?</string>
    <string name="tp_115">Would you rather have the power to grant one wish for yourself or three wishes for other people?</string>
    <string name="tp_116">Would you rather discover everything about me from the beginning or learn to know me throughout your life?</string>
    <string name="tp_117">Would you rather be reborn in a new life forgetting everything about this one or live eternally in your current life?</string>
    <string name="tp_118">Would you rather love come unexpectedly or be the result of a long journey?</string>
    <string name="tp_119">Would you rather love with passion but risk suffering or love cautiously and never get hurt?</string>
    <string name="tp_12">Would you rather always say what you think or never be able to speak again?</string>
    <string name="tp_120">Would you rather have a relationship that soothes you or a relationship that stimulates you?</string>
    <string name="tp_121">Would you rather relive our first kiss or hear \'I love you\' from me for the first time again?</string>
    <string name="tp_122">Would you rather know in advance how all your relationships (friendly, romantic) will end, or live in uncertainty?</string>
    <string name="tp_123">Would you rather live in a world where everyone thinks like you, or in a world where no one ever agrees?</string>
    <string name="tp_124">Would you rather I surprise you every day or reassure you every day?</string>
    <string name="tp_125">Would you rather love with your heart or with your head?</string>
    <string name="tp_126">Would you rather build a solid future or live a magical present with an uncertain future?</string>
    <string name="tp_127">Would you rather have the answer to \'are we alone in the universe?\' or \'what happens after death?\'</string>
    <string name="tp_128">Would you rather have love but no peace or peace but no love?</string>
    <string name="tp_129">Would you rather erase one regret from your life or add one perfect happy memory?</string>
    <string name="tp_13">Would you rather be loved but misunderstood or understood but not loved?</string>
    <string name="tp_130">Would you rather live a long-distance love that lasts or a close love that fades quickly?</string>
    <string name="tp_131">Would you rather have love that makes you better or love that accepts you as you are?</string>
    <string name="tp_132">Would you rather lose all your memories related to your family or all those related to your friends?</string>
    <string name="tp_133">Would you rather know what your pet really thinks of you or never know?</string>
    <string name="tp_134">Would you rather live in a world without music or in a world without books?</string>
    <string name="tp_135">Would you rather have an Undo Send button for real-life conversations or a Replay button for the best moments of your life?</string>
    <string name="tp_136">Would you rather fall in love with a voice or with a look?</string>
    <string name="tp_137">Would you rather discover that your life is a dream or that you\'re a character in a novel?</string>
    <string name="tp_138">Would you rather receive surprise gifts or spend quality time together?</string>
    <string name="tp_139">Would you rather miss me often, or have me always (sometimes too much) by your side?</string>
    <string name="tp_14">Would you rather live without music or without movies?</string>
    <string name="tp_140">Would you rather resolve a conflict right away or wait until we\'re calm to talk about it?</string>
    <string name="tp_141">Would you rather build a house together or travel the world together?</string>
    <string name="tp_142">Would you rather cook together and have a good time or order takeout and relax together?</string>
    <string name="tp_143">Would you rather live a simple and sincere relationship or an intense and complex one?</string>
    <string name="tp_144">Would you rather have clear goals together for the future or live more day by day?</string>
    <string name="tp_145">Would you rather have a relationship full of rituals or surprises?</string>
    <string name="tp_146">Would you rather say I love you often or show it only through actions?</string>
    <string name="tp_147">Would you rather each go out separately with friends or go out together more often?</string>
    <string name="tp_148">Would you rather be complimented on your intelligence or your appearance?</string>
    <string name="tp_149">Would you rather do sports together or share creative activities?</string>
    <string name="tp_15">Would you rather lose your sight or lose your memories?</string>
    <string name="tp_150">Would you rather love be a choice, or something that feels obvious?</string>
    <string name="tp_151">Would you rather have love that teaches you to know yourself or love that helps you forget your past?</string>
    <string name="tp_152">Would you rather keep some small secrets or share everything without exception?</string>
    <string name="tp_153">Would you rather reconcile after a fight with a big hug or a calm discussion?</string>
    <string name="tp_154">Would you rather go on a road trip with no money with your friends or on a luxury vacation with your family?</string>
    <string name="tp_155">Would you rather your best friend date your ex or hide a huge mistake from you?</string>
    <string name="tp_156">Would you rather organize a surprise party for a friend or have one organized for you?</string>
    <string name="tp_157">Would you rather your friends always tell you the truth, even if it hurts, or sugar-coat things a bit?</string>
    <string name="tp_158">Would you rather love arrive too early or too late in your life?</string>
    <string name="tp_159">Would you rather love change you or reveal you?</string>
    <string name="tp_16">Would you rather throw up on your favorite celebrity or have your favorite celebrity throw up on you?</string>
    <string name="tp_160">Would you rather have a board game night or an evening deeply discussing everything and nothing?</string>
    <string name="tp_161">Would you rather your love grow through trials or through sweetness?</string>
    <string name="tp_162">Would you rather be friends with someone very different from you or very similar?</string>
    <string name="tp_163">Would you rather be very rich but alone, or have little money but be surrounded by love?</string>
    <string name="tp_164">Would you rather go back to the past to correct a mistake or see your future in 10 years?</string>
    <string name="tp_165">Would you rather be famous for something you didn\'t do or unknown despite an incredible feat?</string>
    <string name="tp_166">Would you rather sacrifice your personal happiness for the common good or prioritize yourself?</string>
    <string name="tp_167">Would you rather the other find you physically or mentally irresistible?</string>
    <string name="tp_168">Would you rather live a short and intense life or a long but somewhat monotonous life?</string>
    <string name="tp_169">Would you rather easily forgive someone who hurt you or hold a grudge for a long time?</string>
    <string name="tp_17">Would you rather never have internet again or never be able to fly again?</string>
    <string name="tp_170">Would you rather read others\' minds (hear everything) or have them be able to read yours?</string>
    <string name="tp_171">Would you rather live a life full of different loves or one story that transcends time?</string>
    <string name="tp_172">Would you rather have a passionate but very poorly paid job or a boring but very well-paid job?</string>
    <string name="tp_173">Would you rather I could read your heart or read your thoughts?</string>
    <string name="tp_174">Would you rather have the answer to all scientific questions or all philosophical questions?</string>
    <string name="tp_175">Would you rather be respected or be loved?</string>
    <string name="tp_176">Would you rather live under the sea or in space?</string>
    <string name="tp_177">Would you rather live without your phone or without your computer?</string>
    <string name="tp_178">Would you rather have love that surprises you or that secures you?</string>
    <string name="tp_179">Would you rather spend a year in prison or a year on the streets?</string>
    <string name="tp_18">Would you rather be a king/queen 1,000 years ago or an ordinary person today?</string>
    <string name="tp_180">Would you rather be on a losing team with your friends or on the rival team and win?</string>
    <string name="tp_181">Would you rather I be your first message of the morning or your last of the evening?</string>
    <string name="tp_182">Would you rather solve climate change or end all conflicts in the world?</string>
    <string name="tp_183">Would you rather have a partner who challenges you or who reassures you?</string>
    <string name="tp_184">Would you rather our relationship be like fireworks, or like a cozy fireplace?</string>
    <string name="tp_185">Would you rather cheat at a game and win or lose knowing you gave everything?</string>
    <string name="tp_186">Would you rather eat at your usual favorite restaurant or try a new one that just opened?</string>
    <string name="tp_187">Would you rather lend â‚¬500 to someone without them returning it or borrow â‚¬500 from someone without ever returning it?</string>
    <string name="tp_188">Would you rather I know you by heart or rediscover you every day?</string>
    <string name="tp_189">Would you rather write a book together or live a song together?</string>
    <string name="tp_19">Would you rather relax by the pool or on the beach?</string>
    <string name="tp_190">Would you rather love, or be loved?</string>
    <string name="tp_191">Would you rather lose your sight or lose your memory?</string>
    <string name="tp_192">Would you rather lose all your teeth or all your hair?</string>
    <string name="tp_193">Would you rather never use social media again or never watch movies again?</string>
    <string name="tp_194">Would you rather spend your weekends indoors or outdoors?</string>
    <string name="tp_195">Would you rather be the smartest or the funniest person in the room?</string>
    <string name="tp_196">Would you rather love like the first day or love better each day?</string>
    <string name="tp_197">Would you rather never doubt again or never be afraid again?</string>
    <string name="tp_198">Would you rather our relationship be a haven of peace or a great adventure?</string>
    <string name="tp_199">Would you rather meet famous people today or those who will become famous in a year?</string>
    <string name="tp_2">Would you rather share all your childhood memories or all your future dreams?</string>
    <string name="tp_20">Would you rather live without love or live without friendship?</string>
    <string name="tp_200">Would you rather our love be sung in a song or painted in a painting?</string>
    <string name="tp_201">Would you rather our love be a constant refuge or a perpetual source of challenges?</string>
    <string name="tp_202">Would you rather every kiss say \'I love you\' or \'I understand you\'?</string>
    <string name="tp_203">Would you rather always be the center of attention or stay discreet during gatherings?</string>
    <string name="tp_204">Would you rather have a small circle of close friends or a large group of acquaintances?</string>
    <string name="tp_205">Would you rather attend a party where you know everyone but it\'s boring or a lively party with strangers?</string>
    <string name="tp_206">Would you rather we part with a smile or stay together in doubt?</string>
    <string name="tp_207">Would you rather I know your entire past or only your present?</string>
    <string name="tp_208">Would you rather have a long-distance relationship full of messages or a close one with little communication?</string>
    <string name="tp_209">Would you rather always have to publicly announce your personal successes or keep them completely secret?</string>
    <string name="tp_21">Would you rather find a rat in your kitchen or a cockroach in your bed?</string>
    <string name="tp_210">Would you rather know when you\'re being lied to or never know?</string>
    <string name="tp_211">Would you rather be stuck on an island with someone you don\'t like or be there completely alone?</string>
    <string name="tp_212">Would you rather never be able to say what you think or always have to tell the truth?</string>
    <string name="tp_213">Would you rather be homeless but surrounded by your family and friends, or live comfortably but alone?</string>
    <string name="tp_214">Would you rather travel to the past to meet your ancestors or to the future to meet your descendants?</string>
    <string name="tp_215">Would you rather always arrive 10 minutes late or 2 hours early to every appointment?</string>
    <string name="tp_216">Would you rather our story be told or kept secret?</string>
    <string name="tp_217">Would you rather be right in an argument or make peace quickly?</string>
    <string name="tp_218">Would you rather participate in a reality TV show that films your life 24/7 or live alone in total isolation?</string>
    <string name="tp_219">Would you rather have love that arrives too early or takes too long to come?</string>
    <string name="tp_22">Would you rather have a pause button or a rewind button in your life?</string>
    <string name="tp_220">Would you rather live in a hot or cold place all year round?</string>
    <string name="tp_221">Would you rather have a partner who\'s always honest even when it hurts or a liar who doesn\'t hurt you?</string>
    <string name="tp_222">Would you rather have a relationship full of projects or full of adventure?</string>
    <string name="tp_223">Would you rather live a wonderful life until 100, or spend 100 years at the age of your choice?</string>
    <string name="tp_224">Would you rather be reborn in the same country or in another of your choice?</string>
    <string name="tp_225">Would you rather live in a country with four distinct seasons or in a country that\'s always sunny and warm?</string>
    <string name="tp_226">Would you rather live by the sea or in the mountains?</string>
    <string name="tp_227">Would you rather live in a castle with secret passages or in a modern manor with all the latest technology?</string>
    <string name="tp_228">Would you rather follow a strict routine every day or have total spontaneity in your schedule?</string>
    <string name="tp_229">Would you rather always have to dress formally or always wear casual clothes?</string>
    <string name="tp_23">Would you rather lose all your teeth or lose a day of your life every time you kiss someone?</string>
    <string name="tp_230">Would you rather feel like you never do enough or that I never do enough?</string>
    <string name="tp_231">Would you rather be able to eat as much as you want without ever gaining weight, or feel perfectly rested after only three hours of sleep?</string>
    <string name="tp_232">Would you rather be the luckiest person in the world or know that you earned everything through your work?</string>
    <string name="tp_233">Would you rather have a noisy neighbor or a too-curious neighbor?</string>
    <string name="tp_234">Would you rather be surprised every day or understand me effortlessly?</string>
    <string name="tp_235">Would you rather have lots of energy or lots of money?</string>
    <string name="tp_236">Would you rather be a genius that everyone thinks is an idiot or an idiot that everyone thinks is a genius?</string>
    <string name="tp_237">Would you rather hear \'I love you\' often or feel it without words?</string>
    <string name="tp_238">Would you rather relive our first date, or our first uncontrollable laughter?</string>
    <string name="tp_239">Would you rather I show my love through actions or through looks?</string>
    <string name="tp_24">Would you rather die in 5 years with no regrets or live to 100 with many regrets?</string>
    <string name="tp_240">Would you rather always have the right questions or always have the right answers?</string>
    <string name="tp_241">Would you rather have the opportunity to travel around the world for a year or speak 10 languages fluently?</string>
    <string name="tp_242">Would you rather I tell you my dreams or my fears?</string>
    <string name="tp_243">Would you rather be someone\'s obvious choice or their brave choice?</string>
    <string name="tp_244">Would you rather have a relationship where we share everything or where each keeps their secret garden?</string>
    <string name="tp_245">Would you rather have the chance to fix your biggest mistake or never make a mistake again?</string>
    <string name="tp_246">Would you rather be very intelligent or very attractive?</string>
    <string name="tp_247">Would you rather be loved for who you are or for who you could become?</string>
    <string name="tp_248">Would you rather have no photos but remember perfectly all the places you\'ve visited, or have lots of photos but no memories?</string>
    <string name="tp_249">Would you rather I write to you every day or speak to you once with intensity?</string>
    <string name="tp_25">Would you rather know everything about the universe or everything about what happens after death?</string>
    <string name="tp_250">Would you rather be told in advance all the beautiful things awaiting you, or discover them by surprise?</string>
    <string name="tp_251">Would you rather always be in my arms or always in my thoughts?</string>
    <string name="tp_252">Would you rather have a relationship that starts unexpectedly, or one that feels meant to be?</string>
    <string name="tp_253">Would you rather love as if it were the first time or as if it were the last?</string>
    <string name="tp_254">Would you rather win the Nobel Peace Prize or 5 million dollars?</string>
    <string name="tp_255">Would you rather be my refuge in storms or my daily ray of sunshine?</string>
    <string name="tp_256">Would you rather never age or never worry about money?</string>
    <string name="tp_26">Would you rather die before or after me?</string>
    <string name="tp_27">Would you rather have a pause button in your life or a restart button?</string>
    <string name="tp_28">Would you rather be able to eat without ever gaining weight or sleep 1 hour and be completely rested?</string>
    <string name="tp_29">Would you rather live a romantic movie life or an adventure movie life?</string>
    <string name="tp_3">Would you rather build a simple life together or live a luxurious life alone?</string>
    <string name="tp_30">Would you rather be the best in a field no one takes seriously, or average in a highly respected field?</string>
    <string name="tp_31">Would you rather hunt and butcher your own meat or never eat meat again?</string>
    <string name="tp_32">Would you rather never be jealous or never be angry?</string>
    <string name="tp_33">Would you rather have unlimited battery on all your devices or free WiFi everywhere you go?</string>
    <string name="tp_34">Would you rather receive flowers every week or a love letter every month?</string>
    <string name="tp_35">Would you rather be able to create your future or erase a mistake from the past?</string>
    <string name="tp_36">Would you rather always be the person who loves more or the one who is loved more?</string>
    <string name="tp_37">Would you rather solve world hunger or climate change?</string>
    <string name="tp_38">Would you rather never fall in love again or always fall in love too quickly?</string>
    <string name="tp_39">Would you rather win â‚¬25,000 or have your best friend win â‚¬100,000 but not be able to give you anything?</string>
    <string name="tp_4">Would you rather let them see you vulnerable, or always have them think you\'re strong?</string>
    <string name="tp_40">Would you rather relive your adolescence or discover who you\'ll be in 30 years?</string>
    <string name="tp_41">Would you rather live a passionate but short love, or a calm but everlasting love?</string>
    <string name="tp_42">Would you rather fall in love with a stranger every day or love the same person forever?</string>
    <string name="tp_43">Would you rather love always be simple, or sometimes have its conflicts?</string>
    <string name="tp_44">Would you rather someone write you a poem or a song?</string>
    <string name="tp_45">Would you rather a kiss in the rain or a hug by the fireplace?</string>
    <string name="tp_46">Would you rather be known in history books for something terrible or be completely forgotten after death?</string>
    <string name="tp_47">Would you rather go back to the past to meet deceased loved ones or go to the future to meet your children or grandchildren?</string>
    <string name="tp_48">Would you rather travel the world for free for a year or receive â‚¬50,000 to spend as you want?</string>
    <string name="tp_49">Would you rather say \'I love you\' only once in your life but sincerely, or be able to say it every day without it having the same power?</string>
    <string name="tp_5">Would you rather feel every emotion more intensely or live without emotions?</string>
    <string name="tp_50">Would you rather live through a zombie apocalypse or a robot apocalypse?</string>
    <string name="tp_51">Would you rather have a long-distance but strong love or a close but very unstable love?</string>
    <string name="tp_52">Would you rather be able to relive a moment with someone you lost or spend a day with your future child?</string>
    <string name="tp_53">Would you rather receive a declaration of love in public or in private?</string>
    <string name="tp_54">Would you rather share everything (truly everything, including me), or keep everything to yourself and leave others with nothing?</string>
    <string name="tp_55">Would you rather have love that makes you dream or love that makes you grow?</string>
    <string name="tp_56">Would you rather be alone all your life or surrounded by very annoying people?</string>
    <string name="tp_57">Would you rather have no phone for a month or not wash for a month?</string>
    <string name="tp_58">Would you rather fall in love at first sight (even if you\'re wrong) or only after three years?</string>
    <string name="tp_59">Would you rather only buy used underwear or only used toothbrushes?</string>
    <string name="tp_6">Would you rather spend a month reliving your most beautiful memories or a month creating new moments together?</string>
    <string name="tp_60">Would you rather lose the ability to read or the ability to speak?</string>
    <string name="tp_61">Would you rather be beautiful but stupid or ugly but ultra intelligent?</string>
    <string name="tp_62">At work, would you rather be loved or feared? Why?</string>
    <string name="tp_63">Would you rather know perfect love in a dream or imperfect but real love?</string>
    <string name="tp_64">Would you rather ask a favor from your ex or from a complete stranger?</string>
    <string name="tp_65">Would you rather be incredibly rich but completely alone, or have just enough to live but be surrounded by love and friends?</string>
    <string name="tp_66">Would you rather sacrifice your happiness for the good of many other people, or put your personal happiness above everything?</string>
    <string name="tp_67">Would you rather have the power to save one person you love or five strangers?</string>
    <string name="tp_68">Would you rather see justice applied even if the punishment is severe, or favor clemency and offer a second chance?</string>
    <string name="tp_69">Would you rather be respected by all but little loved, or adored by few but criticized by many?</string>
    <string name="tp_7">Would you rather know the end of a love story from the beginning or never know when it ends?</string>
    <string name="tp_70">Would you rather love someone without ever being able to tell them or be loved without knowing it?</string>
    <string name="tp_71">Would you rather love intensely once or moderately all your life?</string>
    <string name="tp_72">Would you rather have old-fashioned love or a modern and free relationship?</string>
    <string name="tp_73">Would you rather receive proof of love every day or one immense gesture once a year?</string>
    <string name="tp_74">Would you rather find a wallet full of money and return it to its owner, or keep it without anyone ever knowing?</string>
    <string name="tp_75">Would you rather be someone\'s first love or their last?</string>
    <string name="tp_76">Would you rather have a fusional relationship or a relationship where each person keeps their emotional independence?</string>
    <string name="tp_77">Would you rather live in a perfectly safe world but without freedom, or a totally free but very dangerous world?</string>
    <string name="tp_78">Would you rather make love without love or love without ever making love?</string>
    <string name="tp_79">Would you rather be remembered for your kindness or for your intelligence?</string>
    <string name="tp_8">Would you rather be able to see 10 minutes into the future or 150 years into the future?</string>
    <string name="tp_80">Would you rather be admired for your physical appearance or for the depth of your personality?</string>
    <string name="tp_81">Would you rather love be easy and quick to win, or something that must be earned?</string>
    <string name="tp_82">Would you rather your partner be ultra romantic or super funny? You have to choose one or the other.</string>
    <string name="tp_83">Would you rather have unshakeable self-confidence but be seen as arrogant, or often doubt yourself but be appreciated by everyone?</string>
    <string name="tp_84">Would you rather live a life full of intense passions but also great pain, or a calm, stable life without extremes?</string>
    <string name="tp_85">Would you rather have a relationship full of surprises or full of stability?</string>
    <string name="tp_86">Would you rather be known as someone very funny or very reliable?</string>
    <string name="tp_87">Would you rather your partner be ultra tactile or very verbal?</string>
    <string name="tp_88">Would you rather be fully satisfied with what you have now or always want more?</string>
    <string name="tp_89">Would you rather have very strong intuition that guides you, or an ultra-developed analytical mind?</string>
    <string name="tp_9">Would you rather understand everything your partner feels or have them understand everything you feel?</string>
    <string name="tp_90">Would you rather know the exact date of your death or never know anything?</string>
    <string name="tp_91">Would you rather receive â‚¬1,000 now or â‚¬10,000 in five years?</string>
    <string name="tp_92">Would you rather correct a big mistake from your past or receive crucial advice from your future self?</string>
    <string name="tp_93">Would you rather have a surprise planned for months or improvised at the last minute?</string>
    <string name="tp_94">Would you rather always be called by a cute nickname or always by your first name?</string>
    <string name="tp_95">Would you rather I hold your hand or look deeply into your eyes?</string>
    <string name="tp_96">Would you rather remember all your dreams in detail or never have nightmares again?</string>
    <string name="tp_97">Would you rather know in advance all the good moments to come or all the bad ones?</string>
    <string name="tp_98">Would you rather wake up every morning with a compliment or a hug?</string>
    <string name="tp_99">Would you rather leave a material legacy (money, property) or an immaterial legacy (values, memories)?</string>
    <string name="trust_us">trusting us.</string>
    <string name="trusting_us">trusting us.</string>
    <string name="type_label">Type:</string>
    <string name="understood">Got it!</string>
    <string name="unhandled_authentication">Unhandled authentication</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="unknown_auth_error">Unknown authentication error</string>
    <string name="unknown_city">Unknown city</string>
    <string name="unknown_location">Unknown</string>
    <string name="unlimited_questions">Unlimited questions</string>
    <string name="unlock_premium">Unlock Premium</string>
    <string name="unlock_premium_button">Unlock Premium</string>
    <string name="user_not_authenticated">User not authenticated</string>
    <string name="user_not_connected">User not connected</string>
    <string name="user_shared_by">Shared by: %@</string>
    <string name="validate">Validate</string>
    <string name="waiting_partner_response">Waiting for your partner\'s response...</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="when_in_use_authorized">When app is in use</string>
    <string name="widget_complete_title">Complete</string>
    <string name="widget_countdown_title">Countdown</string>
    <string name="widget_dash_jours">-- days</string>
    <string name="widget_dash_km">-- km</string>
    <string name="widget_dash_m">-- m</string>
    <string name="widget_days_subtitle">1 day</string>
    <string name="widget_days_text">days</string>
    <string name="widget_days_total_title">Days together</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_description">Display the distance between you and your partner.</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_display_name">Love2Love Distance</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_label">away</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_subtitle">Our distance</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_text">distance</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_title">Distance</string>
    <string name="widget_enable_your_location">Enable your location</string>
    <string name="widget_enable_your_locations">Enable your locations</string>
    <string name="widget_large_subtitle">Large widget</string>
    <string name="widget_main_description">Track your relationship with your partner. The large widget requires a subscription.</string>
    <string name="widget_main_display_name">Love2Love</string>
    <string name="widget_map_description">This widget requires location enabled for both partners.</string>
    <string name="widget_map_display_name">Distance Love2Love</string>
    <string name="widget_our_distance">Our distance:</string>
    <string name="widget_partner_enable_location">Partner must enable location</string>
    <string name="widget_small_subtitle">Small widget</string>
    <string name="widget_together_text">together</string>
    <string name="widgets_available">Widgets available</string>
    <string name="years_plural">years</string>
    <string name="years_singular">year</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="you">You</string>
    <string name="you_miss_me">You miss me</string>
    <string name="completion_subtitle">Everything is done</string>
    <string name="completion_title_line1">Thank you for</string>
    <string name="completion_title_line2">trusting us.</string>
    <string name="completion_description">Your profile is now configured.\nYou will be able to connect your partner and start your journey together!</string>
    <string name="completion_button">Start the Love2Love adventure</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="profile_edit_name_title">Edit Name</string>
    <string name="profile_edit_name_description">Enter your new display name</string>
    <string name="profile_edit_name_error">Name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="profile_relationship_date_title">In couple since</string>
    <string name="profile_relationship_date_description">Select the start date of your relationship</string>
    <string name="profile_photo_editor_title">Change profile photo</string>
    <string name="profile_photo_editor_description">Select a new photo and adjust it</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_title">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_message">Are you sure you want to permanently delete your account?</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_warning">This action is irreversible. All your data will be permanently deleted:</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_data_profile">â€¢ Profile and photo</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_data_messages">â€¢ Messages and conversations</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_data_favorites">â€¢ Favorite questions</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_data_partner">â€¢ Partner connection</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_confirmation_data_journal">â€¢ Journal and memories</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_permanently">Delete permanently</string>
    <string name="profile_updated">Profile updated successfully</string>
    <string name="profile_error">Error updating profile</string>
    <string name="profile_connected_to_partner">Connected to %s</string>
    <string name="profile_not_connected">Not connected</string>
    <string name="profile_learn_to_use">Learn to use</string>
    <string name="profile_configure_widgets">Configure widgets</string>
    <string name="profile_write_to_us">Write to us</string>
    <string name="profile_terms_of_use">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="profile_privacy_policy_title">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="widget_days_together">days together</string>
    <string name="widget_error_message">Widget error, please update</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_error">Distance error</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_premium_title">Distance Premium</string>
    <string name="widget_distance_premium_message">Subscribe to see distance</string>
    <string name="widget_premium_required">Premium required</string>
    <string name="widget_unlock_premium">Unlock premium widgets</string>
    <string name="widget_no_location">Position unknown</string>
    <string name="widget_enable_location">Enable location</string>
    <string name="widget_connect_partner">Connect your partner</string>
    <string name="widget_days_label">days</string>
    <string name="main_widget">Main Widget</string>
    <string name="distance_widget">Distance Widget</string>
    <string name="home_screen_widget_tutorial">Home Screen Widget</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_widget_tutorial">Lock Screen Widget</string>
    <string name="tutorial_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="tutorial_previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="tutorial_next">Next</string>
    <string name="tutorial_finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="customize">Customize</string>
    <string name="premium_required">Premium required</string>
    <string name="widget_customize_description">Customize widget settings</string>
    <string name="hold_home_screen">Hold the home screen</string>
    <string name="hold_description">Press and hold an empty area on your home screen</string>
    <string name="search_love2love_lock">Search Love2Love</string>
    <string name="search_lock_description">Find and add Love2Love widgets to your lock screen</string>
    <string name="refresh_statistics">Actualiser les statistiques</string>
    <string name="statistics_last_updated">DerniÃ¨re mise Ã  jour: %s</string>
    <string name="no_statistics_data">Aucune donnÃ©e statistique disponible</string>
    <string name="statistics_loading">Calcul des statistiques en cours...</string>
    <string name="statistics_error">Erreur calcul statistiques</string>
    <string name="statistics_retry">RÃ©essayer</string>
    <string name="journal_map_title">Map Journal</string>
    <string name="journal_no_events_with_location">No events with location</string>
    <string name="journal_add_location_message">Add a location to your events to see them on the map</string>
    <string name="delete_memory_title">Delete this memory?</string>
    <string name="stats_new_couple">Nouveau couple, grandes Ã©motions ! ðŸŒŸ</string>
    <string name="stats_growing_love">Votre amour grandit chaque jour ! ðŸ’–</string>
    <string name="stats_beautiful_story">Une belle histoire qui se construit ! ðŸ‘‘</string>
    <string name="stats_lasting_love">Un amour qui dure dans le temps ! âœ¨</string>
    <string name="my_favorites">Mes favoris</string>
    <string name="add_favorite_questions">Ajoutez des questions favorites</string>
    <string name="add_favorites_description">Ajoutez en favoris les questions qui vous plaisent le plus pour les retrouver facilement et les partager avec votre partenaire.</string>
    <string name="no_favorites_yet">Pas encore de favoris</string>
    <string name="view_all">Voir tout</string>
    <string name="remove_from_favorites">Retirer des favoris</string>
    <string name="remove">Retirer</string>
    <string name="remove_favorite_confirmation">Cette question sera retirÃ©e de vos favoris. Vous pourrez la remettre en favoris depuis sa catÃ©gorie.</string>
    <string name="about_me">Ã€ propos de moi</string>
    <string name="application">Application</string>
    <string name="name">Nom</string>
    <string name="in_relationship_since">En couple depuis</string>
    <string name="edit_relationship_start">Modifier la date de dÃ©but de relation</string>
    <string name="partner_code">Code partenaire</string>
    <string name="location_tutorial">Tutoriel de localisation</string>
    <string name="widgets">Widgets</string>
    <string name="manage_subscription">GÃ©rer son abonnement</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contactez-nous</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">Conditions gÃ©nÃ©rales</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Politique de confidentialitÃ©</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Supprimer le compte</string>
    <string name="delete_account_confirmation">Cette action est irrÃ©versible. Toutes vos donnÃ©es seront dÃ©finitivement supprimÃ©es.</string>
    <string name="deleting_account">Suppression du compte...</string>
    <string name="authorization_required">Autorisation requise</string>
    <string name="photo_access_denied_message_menu">L\'accÃ¨s aux photos est requis pour modifier votre photo de profil. Veuillez autoriser l\'accÃ¨s dans les rÃ©glages.</string>
    <string name="photo_access_error_generic">Erreur d\'accÃ¨s aux photos. Veuillez rÃ©essayer.</string>
    <string name="open_settings_button">Ouvrir les paramÃ¨tres</string>
    <string name="error_image_not_found">Image non trouvÃ©e</string>
    <string name="close">Fermer</string>
    <string name="no_saved_challenges">Aucun dÃ©fi sauvegardÃ©</string>
    <string name="save_challenges_description">Sauvegardez vos dÃ©fis prÃ©fÃ©rÃ©s pour les retrouver facilement ici !</string>
    <string name="delete_challenge_title">Supprimer ce dÃ©fi ?</string>
    <string name="delete_challenge_message">Ce dÃ©fi sera retirÃ© de vos bookmarks.</string>
    <string name="delete_action">Supprimer</string>
    <string name="cancel_action">Annuler</string>
    <string name="loading_saved_challenges">Chargement des dÃ©fis sauvegardÃ©sâ€¦</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_54">Create together your survival kit for days when love feels uncertain.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_55">Write a message you wonâ€™t send to themâ€¦ then send it anyway.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_56">Each of you make a top 3 of the little physical or gestural details you love about the other.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_57">Each write a letter to be opened only if one day you doubt your bond.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_58">Have a compliment battle via messages: one at a time, until one gives up.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_59">Tell your partner they are the most beautiful weakness you love about them.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_60">Take a screenshot of the most beautiful message you received from your partner and send it to them.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_61">Tell the other: â€œI want you in my life becauseâ€¦â€ and complete the sentence sincerely.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_62">Draw an object that symbolizes your relationship.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_63">Send each other a photo of an object or clothing item that has a story tied to your relationship.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_64">Send each other a wish via email for the other, to be sent in 10 years.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_65">Invent a Netflix series that tells your love story.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_66">Today is tenderness minute: you have 60 seconds to tell each other everything you love about the other.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_67">Ask the other: â€œWhen did you know it was more than attraction?â€</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_68">Create your coupleâ€™s flag together: colors, symbols, what it represents.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_69">Ask them: If our relationship were a landscape, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_70">Establish a phrase to say during an argument to defuse tension.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_71">Ask them: Whatâ€™s the phrase I said to you that youâ€™ve never forgotten?</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_72">Choose a song that could be played at your wedding or vow renewal. Explain why.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_73">Tell your partner: Hereâ€™s what Iâ€™ve learned thanks to youâ€¦ and complete the sentence.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_74">Create together a playlist of 3 songs that best represent your love.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_75">Send a message to your partner saying what youâ€™d want your children to remember about your relationship.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_76">Ask them: What did you see in me that I didnâ€™t see in myself?</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_77">Share a childhood memory that makes you vulnerable and say why you chose it.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_78">Each choose a moment when you felt understood by the other. Tell the story.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_79">Tell the other: If I could relive one moment with you, it would beâ€¦</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_80">Ask each other: What do you want me to remember about you, even in 40 years?</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_81">Write a message you wonâ€™t send to themâ€¦ then send it anyway.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_82">Each make a top 3 of the small physical or gestural details you love about the other.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge_83">Each write a letter to open only if one day you doubt your bond.</string>
    <string name="daily_question_52">What is something you find beautiful about me that I donâ€™t value enough?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_53">What is the fear youâ€™ve never dared to share with me, but would like me to understand?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_54">Is there a moment when you felt sidelined in our relationship, even if it wasnâ€™t intentional on my part?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_55">What have you learned about yourself since weâ€™ve been together?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_56">What is your definition of lasting love, and how can I get closer to it with you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_57">In which area of your life would you like me to be more present or involved?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_58">When did you feel that I truly understood you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_59">What is something I do that you love, even if I donâ€™t realize it?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_60">When you think about us in 10 or 20 years, what do you hope weâ€™ve managed to preserve?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_61">When we go through tensions, what reassures you and makes you believe weâ€™ll overcome them together?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_62">Do you have a specific memory where you felt truly loved by me?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_63">What is the phrase or gesture you dream of hearing or receiving from me one day?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_64">When you doubt the future, what restores your faith in our bond?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_65">Is there a specific expectation youâ€™ve internalized without ever expressing, that youâ€™d like to share now?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_66">If our relationship were a garden, what would it need right now to bloom better?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_67">What is the memory we havenâ€™t created yet but that you dream of us experiencing together?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_68">Is there a way of making love or touching each other that youâ€™d like to explore more together?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_69">What would you like me to understand without you having to explain it every time?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_70">If you could share a dream youâ€™ve never told anyone, what would it be?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_71">What would you like me to see as a strength in you, where you sometimes see only a weakness?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_72">When did you need me without daring to show it? And what would you have liked me to do at that moment?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_73">What in our daily life makes you feel that you truly matter to me?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_74">When Iâ€™m tired, what would you like me to never forget to do for you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_75">What is the compliment you wish youâ€™d heard more often in your life, and that I can offer you from now on?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_76">What is your secret fear about our future, and how can I help you ease it?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_77">When youâ€™re going through a tough time, what would you like me to do to make you feel youâ€™re not alone?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_78">What could I do to help you heal from a doubt or insecurity you carry within you?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_79">Is there a word Iâ€™ve never said, but your heart would have loved to hear from me?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_80">When you look back on our story, at what moment did you say to yourself: â€œThis is the person I want to spend my life withâ€?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_81">What part of yourself do you find hard to offer, but would like to be able to share with me one day?</string>
    <string name="daily_question_82">What is the proof of love youâ€™ve never received in your life, and that youâ€™d like to experience with me one day?</string>
</resources>